<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[1747]]></id><name><![CDATA[skrill]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Skrill Official]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Secure online payments for your business.  Take advantage of a modern, flexible, and optimized payment solution- all with one contract, one integration and free setup]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/1747-skrill-official.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1747.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Secure online payments for your business.  Take advantage of a modern, flexible, and optimized payment solution- all with one contract, one integration and free setup.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Free and quick setupAccess credit cards, 20+ local payment methods and support for over 80 banksTake advantage of the Skrill multi-currency account, giving you access to 40+ currenciesHigh-security standards and anti-fraud technologySeamless payment experience across mobile, tablet and desktopConnect with millions of Skrill account holders]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.55]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1570570-pprod/skrill-official.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1570570-pbig/skrill-official.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1748]]></id><name><![CDATA[paypal]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PayPal Official]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This free official PayPal module can help you grow your sales by adding PayPal and PayPal Pay Later options to your store]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/1748-paypal-official.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1748.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This free official PayPal module can help you grow your sales by adding PayPal and PayPal Pay Later options to your store. With millions of users in over 200 markets, PayPal is one of the most trusted and familiar brands in the world.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Activate easilyWith PayPal, you can start accepting payments quickly without any set-up fee.&nbsp;Include Pay Later options at no extra cost to your businessPay Later lets customers pay over time while you get paid upfront. [1] PayPal&#39;s pay later options are helping boost merchant conversion rates and cart sizes by 39% [2]&nbsp;Promote Pay Later on your siteLet customers know they have the flexibility to buy now and pay later by adding Pay Later promotional messaging and Pay Later button to your site.&nbsp;Offer fast checkout with less frictionStreamlined checkout helps reduce cart abandonment, drive conversion rates, and encourage repeat business. With PayPal, customers can use their saved billing and shipping info to check out faster &mdash; on any device.&nbsp;Get best-in-class fraud detectionPayPal helps you handle the risk of fraudulent transactions with our fraud, chargeback, and Seller Protection [3] capabilities (on eligible transactions). Our AI technology works hard to monitor your transactions &ndash; so you can focus on what matters most.&nbsp;Access funds quickly. After a customer completes their PayPal transaction, you&rsquo;re quickly credited while the payment is processing. Funds settle directly into your PayPal business account.&nbsp;PayPal is one of the world&rsquo;s most trusted, and familiar brands [4]Millions of global users20+ years of experience200+ markets around the world100+ different currencies&nbsp;&nbsp;[1] PayPal Pay Later eligibility and availability is subject to merchant status, sector and integration. Consumer eligibility is subject to status and approval. Product features differ by market. See relevant product terms for more details.https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/paypal-payin3/terms[2] PayPal Q2 earnings 2021.[3] Available on eligible purchases. Limits apply. https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/useragreement-full[4] Morning Consult - The 15 Most Trusted Brands Globally. March 2021.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.2.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1012580-pprod/paypal-official.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1012580-pbig/paypal-official.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8795]]></id><name><![CDATA[payplug]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[- Payplug - Accept customer payments, wherever they are]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Cash all customer credit card payments with a single payment solution: on your PrestaShop e-commerce site, in-store, or directly from online customer conversations]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/8795--payplug-accept-customer-payments-wherever-they-are.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8795.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Cash all customer credit card payments with a single payment solution: on your PrestaShop e-commerce site, in-store, or directly from online customer conversations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[One payment system for all your sales channels&nbsp;Payplug allows credit card payments:via your online store (PrestaShop) in just a few clicks;in-store, with payment terminals that meet the highest market standards;through payment links from customer conversations via text, e-mail, messenger, or WhatsApp.Then you can manage all payments from one tool, your Payplug portal.&nbsp;Manage your performance directly from the Payplug portalView all payments in real time;Understand why credit card payments failed;Download integrated accounting reports in one simple click;Generate payment links to be shared via online customer conversations;Carry out bank transfer requests and receive them within 24 hours!&nbsp;Establish your own PrestaShop module to receive online paymentsInstall the Payplug payment module in just a few clicks. Choose the display type for your payment page (redirected, pop-up), and customize the background of your payment page (including colors). Our online payment module is fully secure and compatible with PSD2 - no extra handling is required from you.&nbsp;Handle Payplug directly from your PrestaShop backoffice: for example, you can organize customer refunds.&nbsp;Increase your turnover with PayLaterOffer your customers the option to pay in 3 or 4 installments with or without fees and receive full payment for the order immediately. Fraud and non-payment are 100% covered by our partner Oney.Merchants offering this Payplug feature to their customers have seen their average shopping cart value increase by 45% on average.New: with Payplug, choose the minimum and maximum shopping cart amounts between which the 3x or 4x payment option is made available to your customers. One more step towards optimising your margin!&nbsp;French-speaking supportOnce your payment module is set up, contact our Paris-based support teams with your questions about your online PrestaShop payments.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.6.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1497818-pprod/-payplug-accept-customer-payments-wherever-they-are.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1497818-pbig/-payplug-accept-customer-payments-wherever-they-are.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16769]]></id><name><![CDATA[fraudlabspro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[FraudLabs Pro Fraud Prevention]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Security & Access]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module helps to screen your order transaction for online frauds]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/website-security-access/16769-fraudlabs-pro-fraud-prevention.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16769.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module helps to screen your order transaction for online frauds.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module helps to screen your order transaction for online frauds. The sophisticated and advanced engines help you to thoroughly scan through all elements, such as geolocation, proxy, email, blacklisted, BIN, velocity, and many more to accurately identify potential fraud order. This module came with one month Mini Plan license, that allowing you 1500 queries/month. After the purchase, please contact FraudLabs Pro to unlock the license. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1363071-pprod/fraudlabs-pro-fraud-prevention.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1363071-pbig/fraudlabs-pro-fraud-prevention.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17346]]></id><name><![CDATA[paybox]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Up2pay e-Transactions Crédit Agricole]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Up2pay e-Transactions[1] is a ecommerce payment solution in a secure interface from Crédit Agricole]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/17346-up2pay-e-transactions-credit-agricole.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/17346.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Up2pay e-Transactions[1] is a ecommerce payment solution in a secure interface from Crédit Agricole. You can easily install the solution on your PrestaShop online store to offer your customers a personalized shopping experience  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[For several years, Crédit Agricole has been supporting thousands of French e-retailers with the Up2pay e-Transactions solution that meets their needs and those of their customers.With Up2pay e-transactions, you benefit from all the advantages of a well-known french bank:- One of the most attractive electronic banking commission rates on the market from the start of your activity- Payment of cash receipts into your account on D+1- A single contact person to meet your needs- After-sales support included (email and telephone) based in France Discover our commitment-free offer here.  New : Up2pay e-Transactions Prestashop module is 3D Secure V2 compliant, in accordance with DSP2 regulation.[1] Up2pay e-Transactions is an offer subject to general and pricing conditions, reserved for professionals registered in France, excluding Marketplaces. The Up2pay e-Transactions offer requires a Crédit Agricole account agreement and the signature of an e-commerce card payment acceptance contract including the Up2pay e-Transactions services option.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[7.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1465199-pprod/up2pay-e-transactions-credit-agricole.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1465199-pbig/up2pay-e-transactions-credit-agricole.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17497]]></id><name><![CDATA[netreviews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Verified Reviews ! ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Customer Reviews]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Customers who read reviews are 3x more likely to convert than others. We offer a turnkey solution for collecting, managing, analyzing and publishing customer reviews]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/customer-reviews/17497-verified-reviews-.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/17497.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Customers who read reviews are 3x more likely to convert than others. We offer a turnkey solution for collecting, managing, analyzing and publishing customer reviews.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We offer a solution that will give you a 360 degree &quot;voice of the customer&quot; strategy which includes: multichannel collection, monitoring and moderation platform, statistics engine &amp; verbatim analysis, syndication of opinions, and retrieval of opinions from third-party sources.&nbsp;1. A quick and easy all-in-one solution.&nbsp;2. From site reviews, product reviews, and business reviews everything in our soultion can be adapted to your needs including personalized opinion email requests, campaign deadlines, and how the widgets are displayed.&nbsp;3. Google Partner - display stars in your search and PLA google ads campaigns thanks to our partnership with Google.&nbsp;4. A trusted third party - Our feedback requests are make after the purchase on 100% of your buyers.&nbsp;5. By turning customer opinions into a KPI, you are engaging with your teams in a positive way, engaging in better communication and optimizing your entire business.&nbsp;6. Take advantage of the interconnection between our opinion platform and other Skeepers products and put your customer at the heart of your marketing strategy.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1511155-pprod/verified-reviews-.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1511155-pbig/verified-reviews-.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19512]]></id><name><![CDATA[magnalister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[magnalister]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Connect your Prestashop easily with marketplaces like eBay, Amazon, Rakuten, PriceMinister or Cdiscount.Upload products, import orders or synchronize stock and prices automatically]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplaces/19512-magnalister.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19512.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Connect your Prestashop easily with marketplaces like eBay, Amazon, Rakuten, PriceMinister or Cdiscount.Upload products, import orders or synchronize stock and prices automatically.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Sell more than ever :78% of all online-buyer-decisions are made on marketplaces like eBay, Amazon, Rakuten, PriceMinister or CdiscountThese are the most important distribution channels to increase your sales dramatically. Use your Prestashop in combination with the magnalister addon and make your store a distribution, inventory- and order-management-system.&nbsp;​magnalister is the ultimate connection between PrestaShop and eBay, Amazon &amp; Co.&nbsp;&nbsp;4 main processes supports your daily work:- Upload products directly from PrestaShop to the marketplaces- Orders are imported automatically from the marketplaces into PrestaShop- Automatic stock and price synchronization- Automatic transmission of status like &quot;shipped&quot; or &quot;paid&quot;&nbsp;Many additional features like variation-transmission or usage of different price groups makes selling more easy.&nbsp;Free 30-day trial! :&nbsp;Immediately after the notification and shop-registration, you will receive your personal unique activation key (pass phrase). With this key you can activate and use the software to it&#39;s full extent. No additional or further costs are incurred during the 30 days test period. After the free trial, magnalister costs starting from 29 EUR excl. tax.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.00]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/732056-pprod/magnalister.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/732056-pbig/magnalister.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20221]]></id><name><![CDATA[ndksteppingpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Step by Step products Pack]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Cross-selling & Product Bundles]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sell products from your catalog, by including them in packs composing &quot;step by step&quot;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/cross-selling-product-bundles/20221-step-by-step-products-pack.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20221.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sell products from your catalog, by including them in packs composing &quot;step by step&quot;. This module will allow you to create product packs to compose your customers among selections in your catalog. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase sales of targeted products in your catalog. Increase the value of the basket of your visitors by influencing on sets of products. Guide your customers in the selection of your products.   With this module you create as many steps as you want, each with an arbitrary selection of products. For each step you set a minimum rule adding to cart. Once validated rule, your customer can go to the next step. Once all the steps validated, your customer can finalize the order and receive the discount you have set in your pack!  New: fix a price for your pack, the system automatically created a product pack and synchronize your stocks. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/692955-pprod/step-by-step-products-pack.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/692955-pbig/step-by-step-products-pack.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21260]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartsupp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Smartsupp Live Chat & AI Chatbots]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Support & Online Chat]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Drive your online sales through conversations, and automate sales with Smartsupp]]></description><author><![CDATA[Smartsupp]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/support-online-chat/21260-smartsupp-live-chat-ai-chatbots.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21260.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Drive your online sales through conversations, and automate sales with Smartsupp. We offer everything you need to grow your online sales: AI, LeadGen chatbots, live chat, and much more you can use to engage your visitors at the right time.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Jumpstart your sales and boost conversions with Smartsupp. Our packages offer everything you need: AI, LeadGen chatbots, and live chat to help you turn visitors into customers. Automate responses to repetitive questions and provide a personal touch when it matters the most. Gain insights into your customer service with accurate statistics – track customer satisfaction, agents' performance efficiency, and more. If you want to use one of the world's most trusted live chat and chatbot apps, use Smartsupp.&nbsp; We currently power up over 100,000 webshops and websites so they can better:Chat with customers and build powerful relationships. Our easy-to-install, fast chat box is complemented by Messenger, and email, so every conversation is accessible via our mobile apps.Convert visitors into customers by running powerful lead gen campaigns with automated messages and chatbots.Engage both customers and visitors with our AI-powered sales and care assistants who are always available and ready to help.Understand the conversation flow, how happy your customers are with your team and offering, and what they ask about – but also who converts and who requires your attention. What our users say about us?&nbsp;"Smartsupp helps us to make our online shop even more successful! After a simple installation, we immediately had the first customer with a question, who then ordered straight away."—Oke Harms, Kickerkult.de&nbsp;"With Smartsupp we use one chat in several shops! Thanks to them, we have been able to improve our contact with customers. Communication is instant and convenient for both us and the customers."—Katarzyna, Wujo.pl&nbsp;“70 % of our orders comes through live chat”-Irena ŽIROVNICKÁ, Customer care team leader Unuo Design]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Customer satisfaction: Partner of the year"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-customer-satisfaction-partner.png]]></badge><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1575812-pprod/smartsupp-live-chat-ai-chatbots.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1575812-pbig/smartsupp-live-chat-ai-chatbots.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21293]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazonpay]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Pay]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Amazon Pay offers a familiar, safe, and secure way for hundreds of millions of active Amazon customers globally to complete purchases in your store using their Amazon account - avoiding account creati]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/21293-amazon-pay.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21293.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Amazon Pay offers a familiar, safe, and secure way for hundreds of millions of active Amazon customers globally to complete purchases in your store using their Amazon account - avoiding account creation, re-entering credit card information, and typing their billing and shipping addresses. The performance is continually optimized by Amazon&rsquo;s technology, learnings, and best practices.  What&#39;s New with Amazon Pay? When shoppers check out with&nbsp;Amazon Pay and Affirm, they get more flexibility than ever (US only). &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Reduce friction at checkout: Shoppers complete purchases in as few as three clicks. Amazon automatically recognizes when shoppers have an active Amazon login, so they don&rsquo;t need to sign in again.Enhance brand trust: The Amazon brand is a proven winner of customer trust, and that trust halo extends to Amazon [1].&nbsp;Furthermore, the Amazon Pay A-to-Z Guarantee helps raise customer confidence with buying online.Delivery Notifications: Proactively alert customers on the arrival status of physical goods orders via Amazon Alexa [1]Rest assured with advanced fraud protection: An active base of online shoppers also helps reduce decline handling and fraud risk.Make it easier for international shoppers to buy: Multi-currency support reduces friction in the checkout process by maintaining the local currency experience across the shopping journey and helps customers avoid currency conversion fees from their credit card issuer or bank.Easily and flexibly integrate Amazon Pay into your store: Built-in support for strong customer authentication as required under Payment Services Directive (PSD2).  With 91% of Amazon Pay customers saying they would use Amazon Pay again and hundreds of millions of active Amazon customers already enabled for Amazon Pay, it can help you increase sales [2].   [1]:&nbsp;For two years in a row, The Values Institute ranked Amazon as the top most trusted brand in retail in 2018. Also, in brand rankings from BrandZ by Kantar MillwardBrown and Best Global Brand 2019 by Interbrand, Amazon is rated as the top most valuable brand. [2]:Consumer Net Promoter Score (NPS) Surveys: Conducted by Amazon Pay in 2019 among US, UK, DE, FR, IT, and ES consumers who had used Amazon Pay in the 12 months preceding to the survey launch dates]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.2.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1394406-pprod/amazon-pay.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1394406-pbig/amazon-pay.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24482]]></id><name><![CDATA[sendcloud]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sendcloud | Shipping & Returns Automation]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Carriers]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Optimize your shipping process and exceed customer expectations with Sendcloud, the all-in-one shipping platform for e-commerce]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-carriers/24482-sendcloud-shipping-returns-automation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24482.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Optimize your shipping process and exceed customer expectations with Sendcloud, the all-in-one shipping platform for e-commerce. Create a branded shipping experience and print shipping labels from carriers like DPD, DHL, or GLS in just a few clicks.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Shipping & Returns automation to help your business grow.  Turn shipping from a bottleneck to an accelerator for growth with Sendcloud, the shipping automation platform. Save up to 7 minutes per parcel shipped and provide your customers with a top-tier delivery experience. Sync your account to Sendcloud in less than 5 minutes and immediately streamline your order processing in one convenient platform. Connect to a broad range of carriers worldwide, offer top-of-the-line tracking and returns, print shipping labels in just a few clicks, and more. Get your store ready for international growth with the scalable Sendcloud shipping platform and join 23,000 e-commerce businesses.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1601225-pprod/sendcloud-shipping-returns-automation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1601225-pbig/sendcloud-shipping-returns-automation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24922]]></id><name><![CDATA[stripe_official]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Stripe Official (SCA-ready)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The Stripe Connector for PrestaShop offers a global, scalable integration for payments]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/24922-stripe-official-sca-ready.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24922.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The Stripe Connector for PrestaShop offers a global, scalable integration for payments. Install the connector on your PrestaShop online store, create a Stripe account or connect your existing one, and start accepting payments immediately.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Boost revenue by modernising your checkout. Drive conversion with Link, a one-click checkout experience your customers can complete in just 6 seconds&mdash;that&rsquo;s 9x faster than non-Link customers. Continuously optimise checkout with built-in conversion logic that reduces user friction and adjusts across devices.&nbsp;  Satisfy customer preferences and increase conversion with local payment methods like SEPA Direct Debit, iDEAL, Bancontact, P24, EPS, Giropay, FPX, popular wallets such as Apple Pay and Google Pay, and buy now, pay later methods. Simply turn on over 40 payment methods with no additional development required and dynamically display the most relevant payment methods based on your customers&rsquo; location and device.  It&rsquo;s a reliable and secure platform trusted by millions of ecommerce businesses around the world that protects your customers from data breaches, fraud, and security threats. Stay compliant with PSD2 SCA requirements in Europe with no additional development work.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1581658-pprod/stripe-official-sca-ready.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1581658-pbig/stripe-official-sca-ready.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26957]]></id><name><![CDATA[mailchimppro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Mailchimp for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Newsletter & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Mailchimp is an always-on marketing platform for small businesses.  Create unique campaigns, automate your busy work, get smarter as you go]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/newsletter-sms/26957-mailchimp-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26957.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Mailchimp is an always-on marketing platform for small businesses.  Create unique campaigns, automate your busy work, get smarter as you go. Increase your revenue potential by adding the Mailchimp module for free. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your revenue potentialWhen you connect your Prestashop store to Mailchimp, you unlock features that can help you increase revenue and drive conversion. Mailchimp’s all-in-one marketing platform makes it easy to build and execute multi-channel marketing campaigns that drive sales. Increase traffic to your site and drive repeat purchasesMailchimp tools not only help you increase traffic to your site but with the Customer Relationship Management (CRM) features you can start building stronger relationships with your customers with content that means something to them. Understand what works so you can amplify your effortsWith a connected store, you bring your ecommerce and marketing data into one centralized place. This allows you the ability to understand the ROI of your marketing efforts so you can best optimize your marketing strategy.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1447058-pprod/mailchimp-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1447058-pbig/mailchimp-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27543]]></id><name><![CDATA[nexixpay]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Nexi XPay]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The module Nexi XPay allows you to connect your e-commerce site to the XPay payment gateway.XPay is the Nexi service created to accept online and mobile payments in a simple and fast way]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/27543-nexi-xpay.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27543.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The module Nexi XPay allows you to connect your e-commerce site to the XPay payment gateway.XPay is the Nexi service created to accept online and mobile payments in a simple and fast way.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With XPay you can collect the sales of your eCommerce site by offering a payment page:Reliable, secure and quick to integrate;Multilingual;Fully customizable.&nbsp;With XPay, you can accept payments:From all over the world on the main international circuits (Visa, Mastercard, Maestro, Amex, JBC) and with the most used alternative payment methods (PayPal, Amazon Pay, Apple Pay, Google Pay, Bancomat Pay, MyBank, iDeal, Bancontact, GiroPayetc&hellip;);Also cashing in via a remote payment link (Pay-bylink).&nbsp;And more:Receive the credit receipts in one working day;Free management of disputes and complaints;You have technical and specialized assistance in Italian;Monitor transactions in real time through the Nexi Business App.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[7.1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1548610-pprod/nexi-xpay.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1548610-pbig/nexi-xpay.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[39548]]></id><name><![CDATA[mrshopapi]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ecommerce Native App for iOS & Android]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Mobile]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With this module you can get the native iOS &amp; Android Mobile App for your Prestashop Ecommerce site!Increase your sales, build customer loyalty and send free push notifications thanks to the Mobil]]></description><author><![CDATA[Mr. APPs]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/mobile/39548-ecommerce-native-app-for-ios-android.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/39548.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With this module you can get the native iOS &amp; Android Mobile App for your Prestashop Ecommerce site!Increase your sales, build customer loyalty and send free push notifications thanks to the Mobile App of your Ecommerce.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatic SYNC PrestashopThanks to the integration with your Prestashop store, products, orders, users, payments will be automatically synchronized, making the management of the mobile application incredibly simple.&nbsp;With the iOS &amp; Android mobile App of your Ecommerce you can:&nbsp;✓ Increase sales of your products✓ Reward your customers thanks to free push notifications✓ Send promotions and news on your customers&#39; smartphone✓ Get visibility on the Apple AppStore and Google PlayStore✓ Take advantage of the power of a native mobile app for your business✓ Stand out from the competition✓ Offer an innovative tool appreciated by your customers]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[mobile]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.5.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1509677-pprod/ecommerce-native-app-for-ios-android.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1509677-pbig/ecommerce-native-app-for-ios-android.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[39574]]></id><name><![CDATA[ps_mbo]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Marketplace in your Back Office]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative Tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Explore the PrestaShop Marketplace directly from your back office and grow your business with modules that meet your needs]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/administrative-tools/39574-prestashop-marketplace-in-your-back-office.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/39574.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Explore the PrestaShop Marketplace directly from your back office and grow your business with modules that meet your needs.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Use this module to:  Grow your business:&nbsp;grow your business with new features and improve your customers&rsquo; experience as well as yours.  Save time: spend less time comparing offers with our pre-selection of modules. This way you can focus on what really matters: your business.  - Modules developed by PrestaShop and our partners, compatible with your store. - Useful recommendations to improve your experience and grow your business.  Shop peacefully: the selected modules are developed by PrestaShop or our trusted partners and are compatible with your store.  Install your modules easily: install free modules and the ones you bought on PrestaShop Addons Marketplace with a simple click, from your back office. No need to upload a .zip file! The latest compatible version of the modules is automatically installed.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.6.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.2]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1596702-pprod/prestashop-marketplace-in-your-back-office.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1596702-pbig/prestashop-marketplace-in-your-back-office.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[40307]]></id><name><![CDATA[mollie]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Mollie Payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Mollie is a payment service provider creating solutions for entrepreneurs to receive and manage their online payments]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/40307-mollie-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/40307.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Mollie is a payment service provider creating solutions for entrepreneurs to receive and manage their online payments. All you need to do is download Mollie’s free plugin and integrate it in your Prestashop webshop. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Mollie serves smaller local merchants as well as international corporations. We always look one step further, aiming to disrupt the payment industry. Don’t let borders define your business and offer multiple method payments to your clients.  Focus on the most important : your company. Mollie takes care of your payments.No administrative tasks to get your business up and running with Mollie. You can create your account within a few minutes and start accepting the most used method payments in Europe.There are no hidden fees, no subscription fees, and you only pay for successful transactions.Get the expertise of a team dedicated to your needs. For more informations : https://www.mollie.com/en/ ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1279847-pprod/mollie-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1279847-pbig/mollie-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[42138]]></id><name><![CDATA[colissimo]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Colissimo - Official app: your shipments with Colissimo]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Carriers]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows :the integration of PUDO display on the merchant site,printing labels from Prestashop back office or Coliship, Colissimo label editing tool,an integrated tracking to the customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-carriers/42138-colissimo-official-app-your-shipments-with-colissimo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/42138.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows :the integration of PUDO display on the merchant site,printing labels from Prestashop back office or Coliship, Colissimo label editing tool,an integrated tracking to the customers]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Colissimo-Officiel is an easy-to-use tool that will help the merchant in :saving money, by having a complete solution including PUDO display, a label-editing tool and an integrated trackingsaving time in order managementdeveloping sales on his website with innovating shipping solutions (upselling/cross-selling, international, tracking, mailbox return)]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1296833-pprod/colissimo-official-app-your-shipments-with-colissimo.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1296833-pbig/colissimo-official-app-your-shipments-with-colissimo.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[43440]]></id><name><![CDATA[klarnapayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Klarna Payments Official]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Other Payment Methods]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Klarna Payments official module will offer your customers the choice to pay in parts, pay later, pay now, pay with Sofort or pay in instalments]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/other-payment-methods/43440-klarna-payments-official.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/43440.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Klarna Payments official module will offer your customers the choice to pay in parts, pay later, pay now, pay with Sofort or pay in instalments. Increase your sales and your conversion with Klarna! That's smoooth!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Integrating Klarna on your PrestaShop offers benefits such as increased conversion rates, improved customer experience, risk management, access to Klarna's customer base, marketing opportunities, data analytics, simplified operations, and a competitive advantage in the market.  - Increased Conversion Rates Klarna's payment options, such as Pay Later and Pay in 3, can help boost your conversion rates. By providing customers with flexible payment options, you can reduce cart abandonment rates and encourage more customers to complete their purchases. - Improved Customer Experience Klarna's seamless integration with PrestaShop enhances the overall customer experience. The streamlined checkout process, simplified returns, and user-friendly interface contribute to higher customer satisfaction, resulting in increased customer loyalty and repeat purchases. - Risk Management Klarna assumes the risk of non-payment for purchases made through their platform. This means that you are protected against the financial risks associated with fraud, chargebacks, and customer defaults. Klarna takes on the responsibility of ensuring payment, reducing the burden on your side. - Access to Klarna's Customer Base Integrating Klarna opens up opportunities for you to tap into Klarna's extensive customer base. Klarna has a network of 150M users in the world, and by offering Klarna as a payment option on PrestaShop, you can attract new customers who prefer the convenience and flexibility provided by Klarna. - Marketing and Promotion Klarna offers marketing and promotional benefits to its merchant partners. By integrating with Klarna, you can leverage Klarna's marketing campaigns, co-marketing initiatives, and promotional offers to increase their visibility, attract more customers, and drive sales. - Data Analytics and Insights Klarna provides you valuable data analytics and insights. You gain access to detailed information about customer behavior, purchasing patterns, and preferences. This data can be used to optimize product offerings, pricing strategies, and marketing campaigns, leading to more informed business decisions. - Simplified Operations Klarna's integration with PrestaShop simplifies and automates payment processing and reconciliation. You can easily manage transactions, refunds, and returns directly in your PrestaShop store back-end. - Competitive Advantage By offering Klarna as a payment option, you can gain a competitive edge in the market. Klarna is a well-known and trusted payment solution, and its integration on PrestaShop can attract customers who prefer the convenience and security it provides, potentially leading to increased sales and market share. - Global products, local faces All products are built to be adapted to local preferences and legislations. Last but not least, Klarna provides local support for you and your customers.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.2.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1589278-pprod/klarna-payments-official.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1589278-pbig/klarna-payments-official.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[44577]]></id><name><![CDATA[alma]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[2, 3 & 4 installment payments with Alma, made simple]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Buy now pay later]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase your sales and customer satisfaction by offering them to pay over 2, 3 or 4 installments]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/buy-now-pay-later/44577-2-3-4-installment-payments-with-alma-made-simple.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/44577.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase your sales and customer satisfaction by offering them to pay over 2, 3 or 4 installments.Alma installments are guaranteed against fraud and unpaid installments ; you receive the cash now, your customer pays over time.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your conversion rate and average basket sizeAll payments are guaranteed against fraud and unpaid installmentsYou receive the full amount at the moment of orderBest acceptance rate in the marketBoost customer satisfaction by offering a service they likeDead simple payment page: customers need less than 20 seconds to complete their purchase]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1563234-pprod/2-3-4-installment-payments-with-alma-made-simple.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1563234-pbig/2-3-4-installment-payments-with-alma-made-simple.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[46347]]></id><name><![CDATA[ps_checkout]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Checkout built with PayPal ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Make shopping on your online store easier with our PrestaShop Checkout built with PayPal]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/46347-prestashop-checkout-built-with-paypal-.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/46347.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Make shopping on your online store easier with our PrestaShop Checkout built with PayPal. Accept payments from customers around the world and improve your conversion rate with smoother online payments. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Easy to use  Easy-to-use, all-in-one PrestaShop payment module. Transaction management and history via a single interface Refund management (partial and total) Easy accounting reconciliation.  Optimal conversion  Instantly accept payments by credit card, PayPal, or other locally used payment methods. With Express Checkout, integrate a quick buy button on the product or order pages. By allowing customers to order in half the number of clicks, it can boost conversion by up to 80%.  International development  Accept up to 20 different currencies and sell without borders in over 190 countries.  Secure payments  PayPal protects every transaction to preserve your customers&#39; payment information and prevent fraud on your site. Thanks to the 3D Secure system, the payments on your store are protected against all types of fraud.  Discover our preferential and transparent rates  No setup fees No monthly fee Commission per payment method.  Prestashop Checkout offers you very competitive transaction rates. Refer to our price list for more details about your country&#39;s conditions.  We can offer a custom price for businesses exceeding &euro;50k in monthly revenue. Contact PayPal for more information. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[8.3.5.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1584977-pprod/prestashop-checkout-built-with-paypal-.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1584977-pbig/prestashop-checkout-built-with-paypal-.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[47080]]></id><name><![CDATA[glotio]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Glotio Automatic translation. First language for free]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[International & Localization]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Glotio is a reliable, easy-to-use and cost-effective automatic translation solution that also allows you to translate your store in more than 50 languages available]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/international-localization/47080-glotio-automatic-translation-first-language-for-free.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/47080.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Glotio is a reliable, easy-to-use and cost-effective automatic translation solution that also allows you to translate your store in more than 50 languages available. All this at an affordable and very economical price. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Translate the first language for free.The more you translate, the less you pay. Up to 40% discount for translating several languages at once.Keep your languages up to date. Add your content in your native language and Glotio will automatically translate it for you.Speak in the language of your customers. Internationalise your online shop and increase your sales.Translate like a professional and reduce translation costs.&nbsp;Improve SEO and generate more traffic by improving the positioning of your online shop by being in several languages.Generate data feeds and increase CPC by having your products translated on Google Shopping and other price comparison and marketplaces.&nbsp;International marketing campaigns. Translate any marketing campaigns you want to run to target the language of each market]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[i18n_localization]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.7.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1575479-pprod/glotio-automatic-translation-first-language-for-free.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1575479-pbig/glotio-automatic-translation-first-language-for-free.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[48551]]></id><name><![CDATA[fintecture]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pay with Immediate Transfer (by Fintecture)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Other Payment Methods]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Leader in payment by bank transfer, Fintecture offers an account-to-account payment solution dedicated to e-commerce]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/other-payment-methods/48551-pay-with-immediate-transfer-by-fintecture.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/48551.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Leader in payment by bank transfer, Fintecture offers an account-to-account payment solution dedicated to e-commerce. Take advantage of all transfers&#39; benefits and offer your customers a simple, secure and seamless payment experience.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Generate additional sales and increase your average basket by offering your customers to pay by immediate transfer.&nbsp;Advantages of immediate transfers for merchants &nbsp;A rising conversion rate (+15% on average)✓ A seamless, simple and secure payment experience✓ An ideal payment solution for high average baskets&nbsp;A fast and secure transfer ✓ Immediate payment confirmation to reduce order treatment time✓ An irrevocable payment: funds available between 10 seconds and 1 business day&nbsp;Considerable savings ✓ Competitive rates: up to 40% cheaper than traditional payment methods✓ An automatic reconciliation]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.16.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1433810-pprod/pay-with-immediate-transfer-by-fintecture.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1433810-pbig/pay-with-immediate-transfer-by-fintecture.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[49537]]></id><name><![CDATA[dhldp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DHL Business Portal - shipping from Germany]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Carriers]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With DHL Business Portal Connector&nbsp;module, you can handle the shipment via DHL Business Portal directly from the PrestaShop Back Office where you can produce with a few clicks shipping labels for]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-carriers/49537-dhl-business-portal-shipping-from-germany.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/49537.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With DHL Business Portal Connector&nbsp;module, you can handle the shipment via DHL Business Portal directly from the PrestaShop Back Office where you can produce with a few clicks shipping labels for your shipments.&nbsp;&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With this module you can handle shipping worldwide from the countries Germany.&nbsp;Connect your existing DHL business customer portal account with your Prestashop in just a few clicks. In this way, the shipping addresses are exported directly from the back office to DHL and the labels are returned. The module supports parcel shipping worldwide. Shipping is from Germany. Optionally, you can also store your bank data in the module configuration and transfer them to Business Portal.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1431949-pprod/dhl-business-portal-shipping-from-germany.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1431949-pbig/dhl-business-portal-shipping-from-germany.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[49583]]></id><name><![CDATA[ps_metrics]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Metrics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analytics & Statistics]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Put data to work and boost your revenue with PrestaShop Metrics. Enhance the efficiency of your ecommerce thanks to the integration of Google Analytics and PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/analytics-statistics/49583-prestashop-metrics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/49583.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Put data to work and boost your revenue with PrestaShop Metrics. Enhance the efficiency of your ecommerce thanks to the integration of Google Analytics and PrestaShop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[PrestaShop Metrics is an intuitive tool which helps you make data-driven decisions. It provides a complete view of the business and analyzes store performance with unlimited acess to historical data.  From traffic to sales, from orders to customer behaviors, keep track of your store&rsquo;s KPIs in real time. Access insightful charts and visualize your results over time.  Benefits - Synchronized with Google Analytics (v4 compliance) - Key KPIs for your business - One-stop dashboard - Unlimited access to historical data - Comparison mode - Reporting by email - CSV Exporting]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1585070-pprod/prestashop-metrics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1585070-pbig/prestashop-metrics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[49648]]></id><name><![CDATA[ps_accounts]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Account]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative Tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Link your store to your PrestaShop account to take full advantage of the modules offered by the PrestaShop Marketplace and optimize your experience]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/administrative-tools/49648-prestashop-account.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/49648.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Link your store to your PrestaShop account to take full advantage of the modules offered by the PrestaShop Marketplace and optimize your experience.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time configuring modulesOptimized PrestaShop account experience]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.3.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[49791]]></id><name><![CDATA[bluepayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Autopay BluePayment]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Other Payment Methods]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Autopay S.A. BluePayment plugin enables quick and secure acceptance of online payments by e-sellers using PrestaShop software]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/other-payment-methods/49791-autopay-bluepayment.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/49791.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Autopay S.A. BluePayment plugin enables quick and secure acceptance of online payments by e-sellers using PrestaShop software.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Autopay S.A. BluePayment plugin enables quick and secure acceptance of online payments by e-sellers using PrestaShop software. Install the plugin, provide your clients with their favourite payment channels and develop your online sales.  How do you benefit from installing the BluePayment plugin? Thanks to easy and straightforward integration with our Autopay payment gateway, you obtain the possibility of accepting online payments from the clients of your online store. The installation and configuration process is very simple. In only a few minutes time you can give your clients the possibility of paying for their purchases via their favorite channels. The funds paid by them will be credited directly to your account on a day + 1 basis.  What will your clients gain? First of all, the possibility of safe and convenient online shopping. Autopay payment gateway allows you to use the most popular payment methods, including fast Pay by Link, BLIK 0, card payment or payment by instalments. The key advantage is 100% payment security, which we can guarantee as a national payment institution providing modern payment solutions based on stable and proven technology used by banks and a number of other institutions.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.3.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1514740-pprod/autopay-bluepayment.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1514740-pbig/autopay-bluepayment.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[49837]]></id><name><![CDATA[klaviyops]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Klaviyo]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Newsletter & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Klaviyo, a unified customer platform for email, SMS, and more, gives your online brand direct ownership of your consumer data and interactions—so you can build long-term customer relationships at scal]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/newsletter-sms/49837-klaviyo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/49837.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Klaviyo, a unified customer platform for email, SMS, and more, gives your online brand direct ownership of your consumer data and interactions—so you can build long-term customer relationships at scale, and grow your business on your own terms.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automations to help you make money while you sleep.Dozens of built-in automations are fully customizable, like welcome emails, happy birthday, or abandon cart. Each can have any mix of emails and texts. So while you’re dreaming up your next big idea, customers are automatically getting timely, actionable info. Smarter targeting. Deeper personalization. Bigger payoff.Drive more sales with powerful personalization. Whether you’re sending a drip campaign, a transactional email, or a special holiday campaign, ultra-relevant content can help you boost engagement—and earn more revenue. Get more answers out of your data.Data is powerful—but only if you can find it, understand it, and act on it. With Klaviyo, performance is clear. Pre-built reports answer the marketing questions that matter most. Go beyond vanity metrics and understand what’s driving sales. (Really.) Sync all your store data with a single clickOur seamless one-click ecommerce integration allows you to sync all your historical and real-time data, so you can stay on top of every single interaction people have with your brand. Grow your contact list with engaging web forms.Select from expertly designed form templates, and create engaging website forms that turn site visitors into subscribers with our simple Form Builder.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1527355-pprod/klaviyo.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1527355-pbig/klaviyo.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[49923]]></id><name><![CDATA[izettleconnector]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Zettle by PayPal POS]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Data Import & Export]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module enables you to export your PrestaShop products to the Zettle product library in 3 easy steps]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/data-import-export/49923-zettle-by-paypal-pos.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/49923.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module enables you to export your PrestaShop products to the Zettle product library in 3 easy steps.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Create an Zettle product library in secondsThis module enables you to export your PrestaShop products to the Zettle product library in 3 easy steps. It synchronizes your product stock quantity and product prices continuously. So your product stock is kept up to date no matter if you are selling a product via Zettle on the point of sale or in your online shop.&nbsp;Easy product exportYou can either export your complete PrestaShop product library to Zettle or choose a specific category. Also, you can export single products to Zettle. During the export configuration you can choose if price and stock quantity are part of the export or if you just want to export the products to create the Zettle product library.&nbsp;Automatic synchronizationEverytime an item is sold in your store or online, the product data gets synchronized between PrestaShop and Zettle. The module is providing full control how the synchronization is performed. Automatically, manually or by setting up a cronjob.If you are using the manual sync, you will get a full overview of the product data changes before you perform the update.&nbsp;If an error occurs during synchronization, you will receive a push email notification.&nbsp;Import Zettle orders to PrestaShopOrders that have been completed on Zettle will be imported to PrestaShop automatically. This module enables you to have all orders in one place. Synchronization historyYou can review all completed product export and product synchronization events.&nbsp;SecurityThe communication between Zettle and PrestaShop is based on the Zettle API. Any critical credentials are encrypted using the latest industry standard.&nbsp;&nbsp;The services include:&nbsp;Zettle, a member of the PayPal family, is on a mission to help small businesses succeed in a world of giants – enabling people like you to accept in-person cash, cards, contactless and mobile payments. It also helps you to easily organise your products, track stock levels and monitor sales.&nbsp;The Zettle Reader:The Zettle reader 2 is super-fast and processes in-person contactless payments from credit cards, debit cards and American Express, as well as payments via Apple, Samsung and Google Pay.&nbsp;The Zettle Go app:The point-of-sale for any business. Seamlessly integrated with the Zettle Reader, it let’s you run your business – on the go or over the counter. Your shopfront and back office – all in one easy-to-use system.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[export]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.18]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1461175-pprod/zettle-by-paypal-pos.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1461175-pbig/zettle-by-paypal-pos.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[50148]]></id><name><![CDATA[revolutpayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Revolut Gateway for Prestashop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Did you know Revolut Business has products for merchants with e-Commerce stores as well? With a Revolut Business account, you can start accepting online payments for your store via the Revolut Gateway]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/50148-revolut-gateway-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/50148.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Did you know Revolut Business has products for merchants with e-Commerce stores as well? With a Revolut Business account, you can start accepting online payments for your store via the Revolut Gateway module! This module allows all customers, not just those who use Revolut, to pay using their Visa and Mastercard or their Revolut card. With Revolut Business, you can accept card payments in up to 18 currencies and benefit from next-day settlement, and manage all your business finances in one place.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Great pricing:Pocket more of what you earn with competitive pricing for businesses of all sizesGet started with processing rates of 1% + &pound;/&euro;0.20 for local, consumer cards, and 2.8% + &pound;/&euro;0.20 for all other cardsDon&rsquo;t pay extra for accepting different currencies (exchange fees may apply), next-day settlement, or fraud monitoring Improved checkout conversion:Complete sales more quickly and increase conversions by enabling hassle-free Revolut Pay, which lets customers check out in just one clickEarn profit more efficiently by increasing your payment authorisation rates via Revolut Pay compared to card payments Power your international commerce:Accept payments in up to 18 currencies via card and 27 currencies via Revolut Pay using dedicated currency accountsHold and exchange 25+ currencies with competitive feesManage currency exchange market risk by getting a fixed rate for future exchanges, depending on your Revolut Business plan Settlement and security:Get your earnings deposited directly to your Merchant account&nbsp;Reduce your risk of fraud by relying on Revolut Business&rsquo;s fraud monitoring tools that can flag early signsRely on a payment product that&rsquo;s both encrypted and PCI DSS certified Revolut pay:Give your customers a one-click, easy checkout experience with Revolut Pay and enjoy higher acceptance rates on top of lower transaction feesYour customers who don&rsquo;t use Revolut yet can earn up to&nbsp; &pound;/&euro;20 cashback rewards when they use Revolut Pay to check out with you and sign up to Revolut (T&amp;Cs apply)Get your money within 24 hours for Revolut Pay transactions Keep everything in one place:Enjoy a top-notch user experience with a single platform for both your Merchant and Business accountsAccess our various business features, including seamless cross-border payments and transfersManage all your business&rsquo;s finances in one place, via mobile or webEmpower your team and control spend with physical and virtual company debit cards, so employees can get what they needSet spend limits on cards, check real-time analytics that help you increase visibility, and more]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1449469-pprod/revolut-gateway-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1449469-pbig/revolut-gateway-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[50291]]></id><name><![CDATA[ps_facebook]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Social with Facebook & Instagram]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Products on Facebook & Social Networks]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Turn your followers on Facebook and Instagram into buyers with PrestaShop Social. Build your way to successful data-driven marketing using the power of the Meta Pixel and the Conversions API]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/products-on-facebook-social-networks/50291-prestashop-social-with-facebook-instagram.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/50291.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Turn your followers on Facebook and Instagram into buyers with PrestaShop Social. Build your way to successful data-driven marketing using the power of the Meta Pixel and the Conversions API.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[PrestaShop Social allows you to easily feature your products on Facebook and Instagram so that more people can find and buy them. Create ads campaigns using the best out of Facebook&rsquo;s advertising technology to increase your traffic: only display your ads to the shoppers most likely to buy from you.  Analyze the performance of your campaigns by managing your data. The Conversions API allows you to control what data you share and when you share it, as well as offer your customers more transparency by respecting their confidentiality requests.  Benefits of PrestaShop Social  - Easy to install -Automatic product catalog sync with Facebook - Automatic installation of the Meta Pixel and the Conversion API - Data sharing control - Launch and management of dynamic ads campaigns - Messenger integration]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.33.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.3]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1585911-pprod/prestashop-social-with-facebook-instagram.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1585911-pbig/prestashop-social-with-facebook-instagram.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[50756]]></id><name><![CDATA[ps_eventbus]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[ps_eventbus]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative Tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[PS EventBus is a companion module that is automatically deployed as a dependency when specific modules are installed on your PrestaShop store (see the list of modules concerned in the &quot;Features&q]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/administrative-tools/50756-pseventbus.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/50756.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[PS EventBus is a companion module that is automatically deployed as a dependency when specific modules are installed on your PrestaShop store (see the list of modules concerned in the &quot;Features&quot; tab). The PS EventBus module enables the synchronisation of technical and non-personal data between your shop and these other modules installed on your shop. This synchronisation is necessary for the good operation of the modules concerned. Uninstalling the PS EventBus module may cause these modules to crash or even stop working completely.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[51721]]></id><name><![CDATA[growaffiliate]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Grow by Tradedoubler - Easy Affiliate Marketing]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEA SEM (paid advertising) & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Grow is a self-service, performance-based, affiliate marketing solution for small businesses and start-ups wanting to increase online visibility, traffic, and product sales]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/sea-paid-advertising-affiliation-platforms/51721-grow-by-tradedoubler-easy-affiliate-marketing.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/51721.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Grow is a self-service, performance-based, affiliate marketing solution for small businesses and start-ups wanting to increase online visibility, traffic, and product sales.&nbsp;Download our module for a 1 stop shop for all your technical requirements]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Grow is built on Tradedoubler&#39;s affiliate network of over 180,000 active affiliates.&nbsp;The Grow PrestaShop Module allows you to set up and manage your Grow affiliate program natively, within your PrestaShop store.&nbsp;When you join Grow, we provide you with the tools you need to search for and recruit your own affiliates from our established partner network. Giving you access to over 180,000 partners, who are ready and waiting to promote your business.&nbsp;The Grow PrestaShop module &nbsp;will take care of all your technical requirements by ensuring that your affiliate tracking is set-up quickly and correctly. This module will also automatically create your product feed to the best standard and retrieve your existing discount codes so that they&rsquo;re ready for your partners within minutes of signing up. With Grow affiliate marketing has never been easier.&nbsp;Grow is 100% focused on results, you only pay for the sales that your partners bring.&nbsp;All your activity will be presented in your PrestaShop module, with useful statistics and information to provide insights on traffic, conversion rates, return on ad spend (ROAS), impressions, sales information and much, much more.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1526496-pprod/grow-by-tradedoubler-easy-affiliate-marketing.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1526496-pbig/grow-by-tradedoubler-easy-affiliate-marketing.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[85751]]></id><name><![CDATA[psxmarketingwithgoogle]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Marketing with Google ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Promotions & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[You don&#39;t need to be an expert to promote your products on Google]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/promotions-marketing/85751-prestashop-marketing-with-google-.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/85751.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[You don&#39;t need to be an expert to promote your products on Google. Get more interested shoppers by showing your products across Google channels like Search, YouTube, Gmail, and Discovery on the Google app. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[PrestaShop Marketing with Google allows you to easily connect your store to Google Merchant Center and create Performance Max(1) campaigns to display your products across Google channels.  Performance Max helps maximize your performance across Google Ads inventory using automation, saving you time and driving towards your goals.  Benefits of PrestaShop Marketing - Free to get started - Makes your products visible across Google&#39;s channels - Optimizes your ad placements and budget thanks to the machine learning - Easily imports your product catalogue to Google and keeps it updated -Shows your products to the right audience at the right time  1) In the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom or Switzerland, Performance Max campaigns can be used with any Comparison Shopping Service (CSS) you work with. The ads will show on general search results pages and on any other surfaces the CSS has opted in to.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.61.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Traffic"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-traffic.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1584957-pprod/prestashop-marketing-with-google-.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1584957-pbig/prestashop-marketing-with-google-.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[86153]]></id><name><![CDATA[storecommanderps]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Commander]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative Tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Since 2009, Store Commander, an overlay of the PrestaShop back office helps you save your time daily thanks to its mass data management: catalog, orders and customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/administrative-tools/86153-store-commander.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/86153.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Since 2009, Store Commander, an overlay of the PrestaShop back office helps you save your time daily thanks to its mass data management: catalog, orders and customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Why choose StoreCommander ?&nbsp;Prestashop expert for over 10 years, Store Commander suits all merchant types, adapts to all screens (PC/MAC/Tab) for an unlimited number of users and workstations.&nbsp;Our ESSENTIALS will help you:&nbsp;Mass updating your data (prices, images, orders, customers&hellip;)Importing and Exporting CSV files seamlessly&nbsp;Maintaining and securing your data through FixmyPrestaShop : the control tower of your e-shopHelping data migrationPlanning easily promotions, sales and controlling your margins&nbsp;&nbsp;But that is not all ! With Store Commander you will be able to carry out many other relevant actions, such as :&nbsp;Driving order creation (Increasing shopping basket, pushing additional sales&hellip;)Segmenting the data for targeted marketing actions (Creation of customer types)Managing MultiShop seamlesslyGenerating PDF catalogManaging&nbsp; advanced export of customers and orders&nbsp;And many more features that you are welcome to test in our virtual online shop (Click the Demo button above) or straight on your shop with a 7 day free-trial period.&nbsp;Your concerns are ours!From creation to support service including development, Store Commander is a team of professionals listening carefully to its users. Do not hesitate to solicit us!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1508544-pprod/store-commander.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1508544-pbig/store-commander.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[86867]]></id><name><![CDATA[motive]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Motive Commerce Search]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Search & Filters]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[E-commerce search that builds trust &amp; sells more. Boost conversions and customer loyalty without compromising on privacy or your shop&rsquo;s search experience]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/search-filters/86867-motive-commerce-search.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/86867.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[E-commerce search that builds trust &amp; sells more. Boost conversions and customer loyalty without compromising on privacy or your shop&rsquo;s search experience.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Sell more and become a digital trust pioneer todayMotive Commerce Search has been designed to deliver exceptional experiences for you and your shoppers:&nbsp;Unmatched search relevancyTrust-first, tracker free technology&nbsp;Full alignment with data protection regulations&nbsp;No-code visual customisations&nbsp;Advanced CSS options&nbsp;Features designed to enable growth&nbsp;Mobile-first design&nbsp;Team collaboration&nbsp;The technology behind the world&#39;s biggest brands&nbsp;Motive Commerce Search is built on the technology of Empathy.co, which provides some of the world&rsquo;s largest online retailers with their search. Motive Commerce Search has taken this same technology and made it available for any sized shop. That means search that is affordable with features that have been carefully developed with the needs of your shop and customers in mind.&nbsp;Greater trust = Better results&nbsp;Boost revenue: Businesses that generate trust are 1.6x more likely to boost revenue and EBIT growth rates by 10% or more (Source: McKinsey)Added value: Shoppers now value trust almost as much as price, and on a par with delivery times. (Source: McKinsey)Respect customer data: A majority of consumers now look specifically for businesses that have a reputation for protecting their data. (Source: McKinsey)&nbsp;Customer data is a driving force for loyalty and steady growth. The Retail Trust Index from www.ethicalalliance.co gives some interesting results regarding this:74% of consumers believe online tracking practices are intrusive.80% of consumers are aware online shops track and use their online browsing history.Transparency, clear data privacy policies and cybersecurity are the most important factors to trust online brands.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.25.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1563492-pprod/motive-commerce-search.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1563492-pbig/motive-commerce-search.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[87023]]></id><name><![CDATA[scalapay]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Scalapay - Pay in 3, Interest-free]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Buy now pay later]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[What is Scalapay?&nbsp;&nbsp;Scalapay is an innovative payment method that allows your customers to buy your products in 3 easy installments, interest-free, without additional cost]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/buy-now-pay-later/87023-scalapay-pay-in-3-interest-free.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/87023.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[What is Scalapay?&nbsp;&nbsp;Scalapay is an innovative payment method that allows your customers to buy your products in 3 easy installments, interest-free, without additional cost.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[In Europe, more than 3.000 brands online and 5.000 in-store, belonging to different industries, have chosen Scalapay as their preferred partner for deferred payments. Our main objective is to make the shopping and check-out experience unforgettable. International brands such as Decathlon, Shein and Calzedonia rely on our solution with the objective of increasing their sales and their average order value while delighting their customer base thanks to a flexible and friction-less payment option.Thanks to a solid integration with Prestashop, our module increases the conversion rate of your Prestashop stop, your sales volume and - most importantly - builds customer loyalty.&nbsp;Why Scalapay?&nbsp;More sales:&nbsp;Scalapay increases your cart conversion rate by 11%We increase your Average Order Value (AOV) by 48%&nbsp;Scalapay customers purchase with a 60% higher frequency rate&nbsp;More customers:&nbsp;List your shop in a merchant directory made by +3000 brandsBenefit from more than 1.5 million monthly referrals generated by our websiteBe part of our dedicated marketing activities and promote your brand&nbsp;Zero risk:&nbsp;Scalapay will reimburse you daily the total orders received in the previous 24 hours by bank transfer.Don&rsquo;t worry about fraud risk! We bear all risks related to that.Our technology allows us to have the highest acceptance rate in the industry, without neglecting security and compliance&nbsp;&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.13]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1519980-pprod/scalapay-pay-in-3-interest-free.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1519980-pbig/scalapay-pay-in-3-interest-free.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[87547]]></id><name><![CDATA[humm]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[humm Payment Gateway]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Buy now pay later]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Founded in Australia, humm&reg; has been offering customers a responsible and trusted way to pay for over 30 years]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/buy-now-pay-later/87547-humm-payment-gateway.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/87547.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Founded in Australia, humm&reg; has been offering customers a responsible and trusted way to pay for over 30 years. humm&reg; is an innovative way consumers can make important life purchases and split the costs of essential items.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Offer consumers payment choice and increase sales and transaction value whilst building brand loyalty and seeing basket abandonment plummet.&nbsp;The Official humm&reg; module for PrestaShop is an easy-to-use module that adds humm&reg; as a payment method to your UK, IE or Canada eCommerce store. Download it today and get your sales humming.&nbsp;&middot;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Catering to &quot;little things&quot; and &quot;big things&quot; i.e. small to large purchases 1-30,000 (depending on currency and country)&middot; Risk-free payment to the merchants (the next business day)&middot;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; In house developers to assist with &nbsp;any questions&middot;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Extensive marketing assets available to help promote the benefits of the service&middot;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Dedicated account management&middot;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Bespoke merchant back end portal available to help you get the best out of humm&reg;&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[0.7.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1527079-pprod/humm-payment-gateway.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1527079-pbig/humm-payment-gateway.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[88475]]></id><name><![CDATA[emerchantpay]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[accept payments with emerchantpay]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your checkout experience, streamline card payments and accept 80+ local payment options via our global, customisable and secure payment gateway]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/88475-accept-payments-with-emerchantpay.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/88475.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your checkout experience, streamline card payments and accept 80+ local payment options via our global, customisable and secure payment gateway.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[● Leverage our global acquiring, alternative payment methods, fraud and risk management and performance optimisation services.● Save on development time and costs without compromising on quality of your user&rsquo;s payment experience.● Work one-on-one with our payment experts to create your ideal online checkout experience, increase conversion rates and grow your revenue.&nbsp;Pricing&nbsp;Download our module for free and benefit from transparent and competitive transaction pricing.&nbsp;UK&nbsp;Visa and Mastercard debit and credit cards: 1%Commercial cards: 2%Transaction fee: 15p&nbsp;EU&nbsp;Visa and Mastercard debit and credit cards: 1%Commercial cards: 2%Transaction fee: 15c&nbsp;International&nbsp;Visa and Mastercard debit and credit cards: 3%Commercial cards: 3%Transaction fee: 15c]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1551948-pprod/accept-payments-with-emerchantpay.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1551948-pbig/accept-payments-with-emerchantpay.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[88719]]></id><name><![CDATA[younitedpay]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Younited Pay - Pay in several times by instant credit]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Other Payment Methods]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Instant credit solution built for purchases that matter, from &euro;300 to &euro;50.000. Offer your shoppers a way to pay at their own pace over 10 to 84 months]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/other-payment-methods/88719-younited-pay-pay-in-several-times-by-instant-credit.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/88719.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Instant credit solution built for purchases that matter, from &euro;300 to &euro;50.000. Offer your shoppers a way to pay at their own pace over 10 to 84 months.Your payment is guaranteed, we take care of the rest.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The best suited solution for important purchasesDon&rsquo;t limit your shopping experience to payments over 3, 4 or 10 installments. Thanks to Younited Pay instant credit technology that is unique in Europe, your shoppers can now pay their purchases over time for all purchases that matter.Whatever products you are selling: jewelry, swimming pools, electric scooters or solar panels ? Your shoppers will always find a solution that fit their budget, starting from 10&euro; monthly repayment.&nbsp;&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1571392-pprod/younited-pay-pay-in-several-times-by-instant-credit.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1571392-pbig/younited-pay-pay-in-several-times-by-instant-credit.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[89361]]></id><name><![CDATA[psxdesign]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Design]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Modules]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[PrestaShop Design allows you to easily and rapidly customize your website theme and autonomously adapt the appearance of your store, brand image and preferences without needing any technical expertise]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/modules-prestashop/89361-prestashop-design.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89361.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[PrestaShop Design allows you to easily and rapidly customize your website theme and autonomously adapt the appearance of your store, brand image and preferences without needing any technical expertise.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Adapt your branding: Prestashop Design offers you endless combinations of colors, fonts, and styles from the free universal themes proposed by PrestaShop. Create a feeling of consistency across your store elements. You have the creative choice !  Increase your conversion: Your e-commerce design is not only about aesthetics, but also about increasing your brand credibility. Offer your customers a pleasant shopping experience by cutomizing your calls to action, promotional elements, messages, texts, etc This will directly contribute to the increase of your conversion rate.  Differentiate yourself from competitiors: Using a website template is very useful and time saving but can lead to a generic appearance. PrestaShop Design helps you create a unique store to differentiate yourself from competitors and consolidate your brand positioning in the market.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[89362]]></id><name><![CDATA[psxlegalassistant]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Legal]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative Tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[PrestaShop Legal]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/administrative-tools/89362-prestashop-legal.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89362.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[PrestaShop Legal]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.7]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[89363]]></id><name><![CDATA[vivawalletsmartcheckout]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Viva Wallet Smart Checkout]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Smart Checkout gets better and smarter over time! Sign up with Viva Wallet to get a free payments gateway, your IBAN-enabled local merchant account, and a debit Mastercard for your expenses]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/89363-viva-wallet-smart-checkout.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89363.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Smart Checkout gets better and smarter over time! Sign up with Viva Wallet to get a free payments gateway, your IBAN-enabled local merchant account, and a debit Mastercard for your expenses.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[30+ payment methods. Accept cards, digital wallets, local payment methods, Online Banking &amp; more.Up to 97.4% of customers proceed to pay when using Smart Checkout.Acceptance fees up to 0% by using your Viva Wallet MasterCard.Daily payout of your online sales to your account, even on weekends or holidays.The app is easy to set up and has no monthly fees or hidden costs.&nbsp;Allow customization of the look and feel of your checkout page through a graphical user interface.Reliable, state-of-the-art, cloud-based infrastructure so you don&rsquo;t miss a payment.It is continually self-updated ensuring constant regulatory compliance and constant improvements to customer experience and conversion.&nbsp;Accept multiple payment methods including:Card Schemes:VisaMastercardAmerican ExpressMaestroBancontactJCBDiners Club InternationalDiscoverCartes Bancaires&nbsp;Digital Wallets:Apple PayGoogle PaySamsung PayPayPalPayPal Pay LaterViva Wallet&nbsp;Local Payment Methods:Bancontact QRBitPayBLIKEPSGiropayIDEALIRISKlarnaMB WAYMULTIBANCOP24PayconiqPayUSofortTbi BankTrustlyWeChat Pay&nbsp;Direct Debit &amp; Other:SEPA Direct DebitPay by BankCash (Viva Spot)e-Banking (&Delta;&Iota;&Alpha;&Sigma;/DIAS)]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1568342-pprod/viva-wallet-smart-checkout.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1568342-pbig/viva-wallet-smart-checkout.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[89509]]></id><name><![CDATA[supdropshipping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sup Dropshipping]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Dropshipping]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sup Dropshipping is your all-around selling partner]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/dropshipping/89509-sup-dropshipping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89509.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sup Dropshipping is your all-around selling partner. We help you get better price from reliable suppliers, automatically fulfill your store orders, print on demand, and customize your packaging and labels.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[All-in-one dropshipping service that help you easily earn more and grow your business.Direct SourcingWith a huge database including over 10 million items from 2 million suppliers, you can directly contact and purchase from manufacturers to cut out the middlemen.Profit GuaranteedAmong all the platforms, agents or marketplaces, you can get the best prices here as it is directly from factories.Multi-store ManagementIntegrated to your store on multiple platforms, your orders can be automatically fulfilled.Professional ShippingWe help you ship swiftly to anywhere in the globe, with multiple shipping methods to be chosen from.Chrome ExtensionYou can install Sup Chrome extension to source products on marketplace sites like Amazon, eBay or AliExpress.Mobile FriendlyYou can download Sup mobile app to easily handle your orders with only one touch on cellphone wherever you are at.Dedicated AssistantsCustomer service is 24/7, and available through social apps. Talk to our lovely assistants whenever you need.No Starting BudgetFree to install and use, no credit card needed, no MOQ. Totally designed for dropshippers and only pay when you have orders.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1555460-pprod/sup-dropshipping.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1555460-pbig/sup-dropshipping.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[89528]]></id><name><![CDATA[mbeshipping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[eShip for PrestaShop - Shipping and Logistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Carriers]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Boost your e-commerce shipping with eShip for PrestaShop! A multi-carrier shipping management platform]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-carriers/89528-eship-for-prestashop-shipping-and-logistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89528.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Boost your e-commerce shipping with eShip for PrestaShop! A multi-carrier shipping management platform. Get 50€ discount if you spend 100€ or more in shipping by Dec 31st* via online registration**  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Meet 'eShip for PrestaShop' – Your eCommerce shipping management platform! Experience seamless automatic shipment creation across multiple national and international carriers, minimizing errors and saving valuable time in just a few clicks. Tailor prices and packaging solutions for each order: you can assign custom prices to each shipping category (destination, dimensions, etc.) and set the correct package size for each purchase. Elevate your PrestaShop store today with eShip, download it for free, and provide a smooth shipping experience to your customer!Don’t miss out on our limited December offer: Get a 50€ discount by spending 100€ or more in shipping by Dec 31st*. *50€ taken off from the December invoice.  Total amount to be invoiced in the month of December 2023 for shipping services provided through the eShip for Prestashop application.** Promo applicable only to merchants who entered into the contract from online registration by accepting the T&C "MBE Solutions for Merchants" for shipping service through eShip for Prestashop by 31-12-2023.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1607099-pprod/eship-for-prestashop-shipping-and-logistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1607099-pbig/eship-for-prestashop-shipping-and-logistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[89537]]></id><name><![CDATA[isendu]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[isendu]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Carriers]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[isendu is the all-in-one suite that grows e-commerce]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-carriers/89537-isendu.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89537.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[isendu is the all-in-one suite that grows e-commerce. The only solution that automates all sales: order management, label printing, tracking, integrations with marketplaces and couriers, email and WhatsApp notifications, conversational marketing.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Isendu gives you the possibility to reduce shipping management costs and improve the performance of your e-commerce:&nbsp;Increase the speed and efficiency of shipping management with the automatic creation of shipping labels and quickly schedule carrier collections.Possibility to ship using the isendu integrated carriers without requiring a contact person;Opportunity to compare and select the best rate for each shipment;Automatic validation of customer addresses in order to noticeably decrease the amount of shipments in inventory.Shipment tracking at every phase to manage shipping problems promptly and guarantee an elevated quality of service;Automatic returns management for every shipment created, all from a single dashboard.&nbsp;Isendu gives you the opportunity to increase sales, reviews and customer retention thanks to email marketing and instant messaging&nbsp; (like personalizing WhatsApp) to establish conversations with customers and prospects.&nbsp;In fact, thanks to these features you can:&nbsp;Communicate to customers in real time where their order is in the shipping processProvide direct and timely customer supportIncrease reviews and sales]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.7.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1556102-pprod/isendu.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1556102-pbig/isendu.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[89562]]></id><name><![CDATA[ps_helpcenter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Need back office assistance - sidebar]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Merchant support sidebar in the PrestaShop back office]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/manufacturer-1/89562-need-back-office-assistance-sidebar.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89562.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Merchant support sidebar in the PrestaShop back office.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.12.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[89705]]></id><name><![CDATA[zotaboxps]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Zotabox 20+ Promotional Sales Tools]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pop-up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase your sales and email subscribers with 20+ promotional sales tools from Zotabox. Your package includes multiple popups, banners, countdown timers, coupons, testimonials &amp; social feed]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/pop-up/89705-zotabox-20-promotional-sales-tools.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89705.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase your sales and email subscribers with 20+ promotional sales tools from Zotabox. Your package includes multiple popups, banners, countdown timers, coupons, testimonials &amp; social feed.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[YOUR ZOTABOX PACKAGE INCLUDES:Easy Popup &ndash; to promote your specials and increase your subscribers with custom images, timers and couponsHeader Bar &ndash; to promote your specials and increase your subscribers. Countdown timer and coupons included.Landing Page Builder &ndash; create new landing pages with easeSlider &ndash; slide out box to promote specials, video, collect emails etc.Push Notifications &ndash; collect subscribers and send out push notificationsContact Form Builder &ndash; customize fields, departments, attach files, auto-response etc.Facebook Live Chat &ndash; Support your customers via FacebookSocial Buttons &ndash; encourage followers to join your siteEasy Store Locator &ndash; make it easy for your customers to find youTestimonial &ndash; have your customers promote for youSocial Review &ndash; automatically display your latest facebook or google reviewsNotification Box &ndash; fade in notification boxes to promote your productsStickers &ndash; promote latest news, new arrivals, blogs etcPromo Box &ndash; to promote sales, products, new arrivalsEasy Banner &ndash; upload your custom image and link to any pageSocial Mobile Tools &ndash; so customers can contact you on mobileEU Cookie Notification &ndash; ask EU visitors to accept cookiesBack to Top Buttons &ndash; enhanced, stylish back to top buttonsEXTRA FEATURES:Zotabox is integrated with 20+ email service providers including Mailchimp, Constant Contact, Aweber, Get Response &amp; Campaign Monitor etc.Zotabox is also integrated with 20 + social accounts including Facebook, Twitter, Google Plus, Youtube, Instagram, Pinterest, Linked In etc.Add countdown timers, custom images, coupons, email capture fields to toolsLoads asynchronously. Won&rsquo;t slow down your website.No coding needed. Fully customizable.Google Analytics and Facebook Pixel IntegrationCustom CSS and Custom HTML availableUser-friendly and responsive design.Mobile friendlyTARGETING RULES INCLUDE:Display on Certain PagesTime on SiteScroll Down PageMinimum Screen SizeExit Intent (for some tools)New, Returning VisitorSet Display/Expire DateGeo Targeting]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1581330-pprod/zotabox-20-promotional-sales-tools.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1581330-pbig/zotabox-20-promotional-sales-tools.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[89788]]></id><name><![CDATA[trustedshopseasyintegration]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Trusted Shops Easy Integration]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Customer Reviews]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[More than 30,000 online shops throughout Europe use the Trusted Shops Trustmark, Buyer Protection and authentic reviews for more traffic, higher sales and better conversion rates]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/customer-reviews/89788-trusted-shops-easy-integration.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89788.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[More than 30,000 online shops throughout Europe use the Trusted Shops Trustmark, Buyer Protection and authentic reviews for more traffic, higher sales and better conversion rates.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Building trust - in just 5 minutes!&nbsp;The well-known Trustmark, the Buyer Protection and the authentic reviews from Trusted Shops have stood for trust for over 20 years. More than 30,000 online shops throughout Europe use our Trust solutions for more traffic, higher sales and better conversion rates.&nbsp;The Trusted Shops Easy Integration is the easiest and fastest way to convince visitors of the trustworthiness of your online-shop. The simple installation guarantees product use in just 5 minutes and usually requires little to no prior technical knowledge. With our toolkit you are always technically up to date and have no additional maintenance effort.&nbsp;Your benefit: With just a few clicks, visitors to your online shop can see trust elements such as the Trustbadge or other on-site widgets, can benefit from buyer protection and are automatically asked for feedback after placing an order.&nbsp;Please note: To use the plugin Trusted Shops Easy Integration, you need an existing Trusted Shops membership. You can find out more about the products and benefits of Trusted Shops on our&nbsp;website&nbsp;or by calling: +44 23364 5906.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.24]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1562093-pprod/trusted-shops-easy-integration.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1562093-pbig/trusted-shops-easy-integration.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[89799]]></id><name><![CDATA[smb_edition]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ps_Edition]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative Tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/administrative-tools/89799-psedition.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/89799.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[90037]]></id><name><![CDATA[paygreenpayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PayGreen - The positive payment solution]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[PayGreen: User experience at the heart of payment&nbsp;PayGreen is the market-specific solution that offers your customers the best payment experience for your business]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/90037-paygreen-the-positive-payment-solution.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/90037.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[PayGreen: User experience at the heart of payment&nbsp;PayGreen is the market-specific solution that offers your customers the best payment experience for your business.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Payment module fully customizable to your business and design: &nbsp;Integrate your payment solution as a Hosted Page or as a Remote Page for a unified payment experience, whatever the navigation tool.Customize the design according to your graphic charter for an &quot;in-house&quot; experience for your customers.&nbsp;A single management back-office: centralized accountingUnified customer experience: a single page for all paymentsA single integration for all your payment methods!Select the payment methods you wish to offer your customers on your platformRelaunch failed payments and refund transactions Finally, find all the tools you need for the best payment experience for your customers, whatever your business:Retail Kit : Easily accept and manage credit card payments on your platform, with or without a bank contract.Lunch Kit : Accept meal vouchers and boost your sales with our offer specially designed for online catering.Travel Kit : Boost your online bookings and accept remote payments by credit card, Connect ANCV and Macartevacances from a single platform.Charity Kit : Unlock L&#39;Arrondi Solidaire directly on your payment page and associate your image with causes that are dear to you.Climate Kit: Install a calculator enabling you to show the carbon footprint of an entire online order on the receipt + a contribution up to the emissions to the climate project of your choice. (Coming Soon)]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1590314-pprod/paygreen-the-positive-payment-solution.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1590314-pbig/paygreen-the-positive-payment-solution.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[90110]]></id><name><![CDATA[classysalesnotification]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Infinite Sales Notification]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Notifications & Automatic Emails]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The only&nbsp;PrestaShop Sales Notification Module&nbsp;you need to show live sale notifications on your PrestaShop eCommerce website!!! It is an essential marketing module that helps to create a FOMO]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/emails-notifications/90110-infinite-sales-notification.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/90110.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The only&nbsp;PrestaShop Sales Notification Module&nbsp;you need to show live sale notifications on your PrestaShop eCommerce website!!! It is an essential marketing module that helps to create a FOMO effect on your visitors&rsquo; minds.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Infinite Sales Notification&nbsp;is a PrestaShop sales notification module that helps you create an unlimited number of notifications to create a FOMO effect on your customers&rsquo; minds and boost your sales.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1568566-pprod/infinite-sales-notification.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1568566-pbig/infinite-sales-notification.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[90219]]></id><name><![CDATA[skydropx]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Skydropx: Cotizador y envíos]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Carriers]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Facilitate your shipments with Skydropx, a logistics software company in LATAM]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-carriers/90219-skydropx-cotizador-y-envios.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/90219.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Facilitate your shipments with Skydropx, a logistics software company in LATAM.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With this version of Skydropx you will be able to take advantage of all the functionalities that will help you make your shipments and easily automate your logistics processes.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1570340-pprod/skydropx-cotizador-y-envios.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1570340-pbig/skydropx-cotizador-y-envios.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[90502]]></id><name><![CDATA[ldinstagramslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Instagram feed Slider - Create your custom feed slider]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Social Widgets]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module for Prestashop displays the latest Instagram posts with over 450 design combinations. It provides a visually appealing way to showcase your brand&#39;s social media presence]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/social-widgets/90502-instagram-feed-slider-create-your-custom-feed-slider.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/90502.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module for Prestashop displays the latest Instagram posts with over 450 design combinations. It provides a visually appealing way to showcase your brand&#39;s social media presence. Simply insert your username.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increased visibility on social mediaImproved brand imageBetter engagement with customersIncreased website trafficPotential new followers on Instagram&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1573198-pprod/instagram-feed-slider-create-your-custom-feed-slider.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1573198-pbig/instagram-feed-slider-create-your-custom-feed-slider.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[90923]]></id><name><![CDATA[chatgptcontentgenerator]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[ChatGPT Content Generator + Blog]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[GENERATES, TRANSLATES or REWRITES&nbsp;unique SEO-optimized descriptions for products, categories or pages using ChatGPT AI]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/90923-chatgpt-content-generator-blog.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/90923.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[GENERATES, TRANSLATES or REWRITES&nbsp;unique SEO-optimized descriptions for products, categories or pages using ChatGPT AI. Our new secret weapons:&nbsp;AI-generated BLOG&nbsp;&amp;&nbsp;product SPIN-OFFs&nbsp;will boost your SEO and sales!&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You&nbsp;don&#39;t pay&nbsp;for using ChatGPT&nbsp;additionally!&nbsp;Any language&nbsp;is supported!GENERATES, TRANSLATES or REWRITES&nbsp;the content&nbsp;for products, categories or pages&nbsp;using ChatGPT AIBuilt-in&nbsp;BLOG with the posts generated by ChatGPT AI&nbsp;will boost your SEOProduct SPIN-OFFs generator&nbsp;by ChatGPT AI! Can one product have multiple sales pages for it?&nbsp;Easily!Generate&nbsp;product descriptions&nbsp;and characteristics&nbsp;based on EANStatistics of used word&nbsp;limits for content generated&nbsp;by ChatGPT AICustom&nbsp;request&nbsp;templates&nbsp;for maximum flexibilityEach spin-off product can have&nbsp;individual or common stock, so the product can be ordered from any pageSpin-off pages will be added to the&nbsp;XML&nbsp;and&nbsp;HTML sitemaps&nbsp;of the siteBlog posts have&nbsp;SEO-markup JSON+LD&nbsp;and a section with&nbsp;related productsBlog&nbsp;can generate posts for the specified product]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1590787-pprod/chatgpt-content-generator-blog.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1590787-pbig/chatgpt-content-generator-blog.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[90960]]></id><name><![CDATA[shopylinkerp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shopylinker Catalog Optimizer]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative Tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The perfect complement to your PrestaShop that simplifies the management of the catalog with an innovative visual system and massive actions with which you will get a catalog optimized for SEO in a gu]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/administrative-tools/90960-shopylinker-catalog-optimizer.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/90960.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The perfect complement to your PrestaShop that simplifies the management of the catalog with an innovative visual system and massive actions with which you will get a catalog optimized for SEO in a guided way, drastically reducing the time invested.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Shopylinker is the most advanced complementary catalog management system, it offers you an innovative visual workspace that revolutionizes the way you interact with your catalog.&nbsp;Imagine being able to spot errors intuitively and correct them easily and quickly, providing you with the perfect context to make informed decisions. With Shopylinker, this is possible. Not only does it save you time, but it also simplifies the process with bulk editing actions that you can apply to a variety of entities, from products to categories, properties, and brands. Forget about repetitive tasks and take advantage of our lists of recoverable groupings to optimize your management processes.&nbsp;But that&#39;s not all. Shopylinker goes further by facilitating the optimization of the content of your catalog with a guided system of evaluation of the quality of the information, you will improve both SEO and user experience. The result? A catalog that is not only easily accessible to your customers, but also attracts new visitors thanks to its improved visibility in search engines.&nbsp;In addition, Shopylinker includes an import and export system with which you can create and update the entities of the catalog using digital files. Are you ready to simplify your management process, improve the quality of your content and stand out online? Then, Shopylinker is the solution you are looking for.&nbsp;First month you pay 9.99&euro; without VAT, from the second month you pay according to the number of SKUs in the catalog.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1583460-pprod/shopylinker-catalog-optimizer.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1583460-pbig/shopylinker-catalog-optimizer.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[90992]]></id><name><![CDATA[creativenews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Creative News]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Blog, Forum & News]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Energize your site and boost conversions with on-site notifications! Add captivating news, punchy updates and attractive call-to-actions in the navigation bar to inform, engage and retain your audienc]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/blog-forum-new/90992-creative-news.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/90992.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Energize your site and boost conversions with on-site notifications! Add captivating news, punchy updates and attractive call-to-actions in the navigation bar to inform, engage and retain your audience.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Customer engagement improvement: Inform, engage, and retain your audience by regularly sharing news and special offers.Website invigoration: Bring a touch of freshness and novelty to your site by integrating news into the navigation bar.Conversion increase: Attract your visitors' attention with short and impactful on-site notifications, encouraging actions and boosting your sales.Flexibility: Adapt your news to your needs and your audience's needs for maximum impact on the user experience.Multilingual module: The module is currently translated into French and English, making it easy to use for a wide audience. Additionally, we are attentive to our customers' needs and are ready to add other languages if requested.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1582596-pprod/creative-news.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1582596-pbig/creative-news.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[90996]]></id><name><![CDATA[simplercheckout]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Simpler - 1Step Checkout |Cards, ApplePay, GPay, Klarna]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Simpler Checkout lets your customers complete their purchases in seconds]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/90996-simpler-1step-checkout-cards-applepay-gpay-klarna.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/90996.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Simpler Checkout lets your customers complete their purchases in seconds.It's a one-step, mobile-optimized checkout form that increases conversion rates by up to 50%, letting your shoppers pay the way they want (Cards, ApplePay, GooglePay, Klarna).]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The Simpler Checkout button lets your customers complete their purchases in seconds, in any device or browser and without a password. It's a one-step, mobile-optimized checkout form that increases conversion rates by up to 50%.Give your shoppers the flexibility to pay the way they want (Cards, ApplePay, GooglePay, Klarna) without the need to integrate each payment method - just install Simpler Checkout and boost your sales instantly! Simpler & faster checkout: Simpler Checkout for first-timers is at least 50% faster than the native checkout, which results in higher conversions.Checkout with 1 click for repeat customers: Returning shoppers checkout in as little as 6 seconds! This strengthens loyalty with a delightful returning shopper experience.Optimised for mobile: A simply designed form that fits the shopper's screen and results in a 20-50% increase in conversion rates.Offers all popular payment methods: Simpler Checkout offers a complete list of all popular payment methods: Credit/Debit Cards, Digital Wallets like ApplePay & GooglePay, Klarna etc.Reduce the steps to checkout: With Simpler, the buying funnel starts with the product page, followed by the mini cart page, then the cart page, and, finally, the checkout page. Shoppers prefer the option to buy earlier in the funnel. So, rather than making the purchase after reaching the checkout page, 78% of shoppers would choose to checkout earlier in the buying journey: 21% for the product page, 32% for mini cart, and 25% for cart.+50% registered shoppers: Simpler "kills" guest checkout, as every Simpler shopper is a registered customer. Simpler gives you access to significant amounts of first-party data that can be used for targeting & personalised offers, and can also provide marketers with detailed insight into your customer's.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1594499-pprod/simpler-1step-checkout-cards-applepay-gpay-klarna.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1594499-pbig/simpler-1step-checkout-cards-applepay-gpay-klarna.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91027]]></id><name><![CDATA[ps_edition_basic]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ps_edition_basic]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Home]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/91027-pseditionbasic.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91027.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[8.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[91044]]></id><name><![CDATA[kevin]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[kevin. payment gateway]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Other Payment Methods]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[kevin. is a payment infrastructure that bypasses card networks, letting consumers make fast, simple, and secure payments from their bank accounts]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/other-payment-methods/91044-kevin-payment-gateway.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91044.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[kevin. is a payment infrastructure that bypasses card networks, letting consumers make fast, simple, and secure payments from their bank accounts. Being live in 27 European markets it is an alternative payment method for more than 350M consumers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[One payment partner, many benefits:  Fewer fees, more savings. Cut down transaction costs by enabling direct bank payments. Save time and resources by choosing a trusted payment infrastructure for a fair price. Instant, direct settlement. There’s no need to wait days, if not weeks, for funds to settle. Streamline your finances and take control of your cash flow with instant settlement. Seamless UX. Instead of being redirected to external pages, shoppers can checkout within your store’s environment. Let customers shop with fewer clicks and a friction-free user experience that can help reduce cart abandonment and increase conversion rate. Broad coverage. Tap into new markets and revenue streams with a single integration that gives you access to 350+ million shoppers across Europe. Built-in compliance. From the moment you integrate, payments are compliant with GDPR, PSD2, SCA, and other regulations affecting the payment industry. Security first. Drastically reduce the risk of fraud by providing your customers with end-to-end payments. With our API-based connectivity to Europe’s banks, you can rest assured that your transactions are secure.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1586328-pprod/kevin-payment-gateway.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1586328-pbig/kevin-payment-gateway.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91046]]></id><name><![CDATA[clippay]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Clip]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Boost your sales with Clip Plugin in your online store; it&#39;s easy, fast and secure and accepts all credit and debit cards, as well as cash payments at convenience stores]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/91046-clip.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91046.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Boost your sales with Clip Plugin in your online store; it&#39;s easy, fast and secure and accepts all credit and debit cards, as well as cash payments at convenience stores.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Simplify the shopping experience on your website and accept all payment methods safely and with the support of All the power of Clip and its more than 20 benefits for your business such as:&nbsp;Anti-fraud technology.Accept all cards and cash payments at convenience stores. Offer payment facilities to your customers with up to 24 months without interest. Receive your earnings in 24 hours, 365 days a year, even on weekends and holidays. World-class customer service available 24/7, year-round.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.12]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1583646-pprod/clip.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1583646-pbig/clip.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91074]]></id><name><![CDATA[youseeme]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[YouPay, EPC QR Code transfer and Crypto payment module]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[YouPay is payment plugin. Your Customers can pay with SEPA instant transfert directly on your IBAN or in cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin . Edited by Youseeme a regulated Company in Europe 2022-50]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/Cryptocurrencies/91074-youpay-epc-qr-code-transfer-and-crypto-payment-module.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91074.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[YouPay is payment plugin. Your Customers can pay with SEPA instant transfert directly on your IBAN or in cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin . Edited by Youseeme a regulated Company in Europe 2022-50.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The YouPay payment plugin for SEPA and cryptocurrency can offer several advantages to merchants who integrate it into their e-commerce sites. Here are some of these potential benefits:Customer base expansion: By accepting payments in SEPA and cryptocurrencies, merchants can attract customers who prefer to use digital currencies to make online purchases. This can help expand the potential customer base and increase sales.Reduced transaction fees: Cryptocurrency payments typically involve lower transaction fees than traditional credit card or bank transfer payments. Merchants can therefore save money on transaction fees and increase their profit margin.Increased security: Cryptocurrency payments are encrypted and anonymous, which can help reduce the risks of fraud and theft of personal information. In addition, cryptocurrency transactions are irreversible, making it difficult for customers to dispute transactions after they have been made.Easier international transactions: Cryptocurrency payments are not subject to foreign exchange restrictions or conversion fees, making international transactions easier for both merchants and customers.Innovative image: Integrating cryptocurrency payment solutions can give merchants an innovative and forward-thinking image, which can help improve their reputation and positioning in the market.Commissions: The merchant has the possibility to set the coefficient of his commissions between 1% and 5%]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1583820-pprod/youpay-epc-qr-code-transfer-and-crypto-payment-module.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1583820-pbig/youpay-epc-qr-code-transfer-and-crypto-payment-module.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91293]]></id><name><![CDATA[tooleamazonmarkettool]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Tool]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Amazon Market Tool, will export your catalog, handle your Prime, MFN and FBA stock, prices and process orders with matched shipping templates. AMT is the most reliable and robust tool to succeed]]></description><author><![CDATA[ToolE]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplaces/91293-amazon-market-tool.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91293.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Amazon Market Tool, will export your catalog, handle your Prime, MFN and FBA stock, prices and process orders with matched shipping templates. AMT is the most reliable and robust tool to succeed. Real free plan available.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[As an Amazon PRO seller, you have the opportunity to showcase your product catalog by listing them under your own brand. With Amazon Market Tool, you can create personalized listings that highlight the unique features of your products on a platform that generates a high volume of traffic. This allows you to strengthen your presence on Amazon by offering a more engaging shopping experience for your customers, while also increasing brand awareness for a wider audience.Preserve optimal sales performance with this robust tool and multilingual support available 24/7.With the Amazon Market Tool (AMT), you can effortlessly export your catalog and efficiently manage your Prime, MFN, and FBA operations, ensuring seamless synchronization of stock prices and orders. By leveraging the power of AMT to optimize your presence on Amazon, you gain access to a highly dependable and resilient tool that empowers you to achieve remarkable success on the Amazon Marketplace.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.7.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599506-pprod/amazon-market-tool.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599506-pbig/amazon-market-tool.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91359]]></id><name><![CDATA[klaviyopsautomation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Automation with Klaviyo]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Newsletter & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Address your shoppers like you know them with PrestaShop Automation]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/newsletter-sms/91359-prestashop-automation-with-klaviyo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91359.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Address your shoppers like you know them with PrestaShop Automation. Whether it&#39;s through email or other channels, you&#39;ll have a unified customer platform that puts your online brand in direct control of your customer data and interactions. Deliver tailor-made content to targeted leads, create a personalized and engaging experience for each individual. Say goodbye to generic marketing campaigns and hello to meaningful interactions that resonates with your target audience.  PrestaShop Automation makes it easy for you to use every piece of your customer data to deliver hyper-personalized experiences across channels to increase engagement and conversions.  Download and start your free trial now! Pricing details]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Multi-Channel Reach: Reach your customers through various channels, including email and SMS, providing seamless communication across platforms.  Tailor-Made Content: Craft customized messages for different customer segments, ensuring that your marketing efforts are relevant and impactful.  Automated Campaigns: Set up automated workflows to send the right messages at the right time, maximizing conversions and saving you valuable time and effort.  Unified Customer Platform: Gain complete ownership of your consumer data and interactions, enabling you to build lasting relationships and make data-driven decisions.  Download and start your free trial now! Pricing details]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1589216-pprod/prestashop-automation-with-klaviyo.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1589216-pbig/prestashop-automation-with-klaviyo.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91406]]></id><name><![CDATA[sequra]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[seQura Payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Buy now pay later]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[seQura, the flexible payment platform that will help your business improve conversion and recurrence.&nbsp;The easiest, safest, and quickest way for your customers to pay on installments]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/buy-now-pay-later/91406-sequra-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91406.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[seQura, the flexible payment platform that will help your business improve conversion and recurrence.&nbsp;The easiest, safest, and quickest way for your customers to pay on installments. Join over +6.000 ecommerce and +1.5 million delighted shoppers]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Flexible payment solutions adapted to your business.&nbsp;Your customers in good hands:Cost transparency and clarityLocal support teams to deliver the best shopper experienceSecure data, we don&rsquo;t share your data with anyone or use your information to sell our own or third-party products&nbsp;Obsessed with conversion and recurrence:We adapt to your business, solutions for every sector and buyer profileThe highest acceptance rate in Southern Europe thanks to our own risk algorithm, created and optimized for the local marketInstant approval. A frictionless credit-purchase experience, buy in seconds without document uploadsseQura marketing collateral to support your campaigns&nbsp;Widest flexible payment solutions in the market:Buy now pay laterPay in 3, no interestInstallments, up to 24 monthsFlexi, combines interest-free BNPL with long-term financing in a single purchase experience]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1590158-pprod/sequra-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1590158-pbig/sequra-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91430]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetwhatsapp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Whatsapp  Chat - Contact Us]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Social Widgets]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Let's make it easier for your customers to contact you! Most of your prospective customers are already using WhatsApp]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/social-widgets/91430-whatsapp-chat-contact-us.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91430.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Let's make it easier for your customers to contact you! Most of your prospective customers are already using WhatsApp. It's time to give them the option to contact you in a way that feels familiar and trustworthy.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ Get back to your customers faster in a way they enjoy When someone has a question about your course business, chances are they’re just going to leave your site altogether rather than searching for a support email. With so many options out there, people are too busy to spend time looking for answers. But when you give them the option to easily contact you via WhatsApp right from your website, this feels like a quicker, more familiar way to get in touch. You can get back to them just a few hours later and they will get your reply directly to their mobile device. No more replies getting lost in an inbox with (probably) hundreds of emails!  Offering customer support through WhatsApp chat provides several benefits for merchants. It enables direct and real-time communication with customers, leading to quicker issue resolution and enhanced customer satisfaction. WhatsApp's widespread usage ensures accessibility for a broader customer base, while its features like multimedia sharing facilitate effective troubleshooting. Ultimately, this fosters positive customer experiences and strengthens brand loyalty. Get back to your customers through WhatsAppTrusted Platform Users trust WhatsAppSend Promotions and updates through WhatsAppCustomize Whatsapp - Contact Us style to fit your website]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1590405-pprod/whatsapp-chat-contact-us.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1590405-pbig/whatsapp-chat-contact-us.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91510]]></id><name><![CDATA[bonaicontent]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[ChatGPT - OpenAI Content Generator]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Capture your customers&#39; attention and boost sales with the ChatGPT - OpenAI Content Generator module for PrestaShop! Save your time and energy as our powerful module takes care of all the repetiti]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/91510-chatgpt-openai-content-generator.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91510.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Capture your customers&#39; attention and boost sales with the ChatGPT - OpenAI Content Generator module for PrestaShop! Save your time and energy as our powerful module takes care of all the repetitive tasks for you.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ChatGPT - OpenAI Content Generator is an advanced module developed for automatic content generation. With the assistance of this module, your PrestaShop store gains a powerful tool that automatically generates unique and high-quality content.&nbsp;Improved Search Ranking: Boost your search engine rankings by creating unique descriptions for popular marketplaces. Create a product description for several marketplaces at the same time.Short Description to Full Product Description: Transform short product descriptions into comprehensive ones, providing customers with all the necessary details.Category Description and Meta Description Creation: Enhance your category pages with well-crafted descriptions and meta tags, improving search engine visibility.Rewrite the Name of the Product: Give your products a fresh and captivating name that stands out from the competition.Creating a Meta Title and Meta Description: Automatically generate optimized meta tags for improved search engine optimization (SEO).Complete Product Information is used: Utilize all available product information to create accurate and detailed descriptions.Ability to Edit Generated Results: Fine-tune the generated content to align with your brand voice and style.No GPT API Key Required: Start generating content right away without the need for an additional API key.Flexible Setup: Customize the module according to your specific needs and preferences.What&#39;s more, the ChatGPT - OpenAI Content Generator module offers a FREE plan for users to get started with generating high-quality content without any additional cost. Experience the benefits of this module at no charge!&nbsp;With the ChatGPT - OpenAI Content Generator module, you&#39;ll have a powerful tool at your disposal to create compelling and persuasive content that drives sales. Don&#39;t miss out on this opportunity to streamline your content creation process and achieve remarkable results.Grab the module now and take your PrestaShop store to new heights of success!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1591723-pprod/chatgpt-openai-content-generator.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1591723-pbig/chatgpt-openai-content-generator.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91532]]></id><name><![CDATA[stancer]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Stancer for Prestashop ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Card or Wallet]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With Stancer, develop business online in a secure way.No commitment, no subscription, no hidden costs]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-card-wallet/91532-stancer-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91532.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With Stancer, develop business online in a secure way.No commitment, no subscription, no hidden costs.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ACCEPT A MULTITUDE OF PAYMENT METHODSThe Stancer module for Prestashop allows you to accept the most common payment methods used by your customers such as credit cards, classic or instant SEPA transfers, or SEPA direct debits, to collect them from your Prestashop merchant site.&nbsp;GUARANTEE THE SECURITY OF YOUR PAYMENTSSecure transactions enhance your website&rsquo;s reputation and help your business grow. This is why we have set up robust and reliable protection systems to protect you from fraud attempts.Payments are 3D-Secure compatible. The amount at which the 3D-Secure is adjustable from the back-office module in Prestashop.&nbsp;A DASHBOARD TO FOLLOW YOUR ACTIVITYManage and control your business from a Dashboard. This unique dashboard gives you a consolidated view of cash receipts, refunds and claims. Keep a history of activity and get statistics on your recurring revenues.&nbsp;A SIMPLE, AFFORDABLE OFFERWe have designed our solution to be as accessible as possible so that every company can get the most out of it and grow serenely.Find out more about our pricing : https://www.stancer.com/en/pricing.&nbsp;A FLEXIBLE OFFER, WITH NO COMMITMENTTake advantage of a low-cost online payment solution, with no subscription and no commitment. You are free to suspend or terminate the offer whenever you like, at no cost.Do you have any questions about Stancer? Contact us : https://share-eu1.hsforms.com/13UoWjrWHTxe5PzSLk-hCTAft2n5]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1592235-pprod/stancer-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1592235-pbig/stancer-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91603]]></id><name><![CDATA[tooleamazonclickcollect]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Click & Collect]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Collection Points & In-Store Pick Up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[A new opportunity to make more sales on Amazon! Click &amp; Collect is ToolE&#39;s latest Amazon service]]></description><author><![CDATA[ToolE]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/collection-points-in-store-pick-up/91603-amazon-click-collect.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91603.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[A new opportunity to make more sales on Amazon! Click &amp; Collect is ToolE&#39;s latest Amazon service. The &quot;In-Store Pickup&quot; option is displayed on Amazon for pickup in YOUR store or WAREHOUSE.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Be first on the Buy BoxGet more traffic into your local store.Create a more personal relationship with your existing and new customersGet more items to the shopping cartUp your sales with more optionsKeep your picked-up inventory separated &amp; organizedInstant order retrieving, order notificationsAutomatic refunds possible if no-show]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.7.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599663-pprod/amazon-click-collect.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599663-pbig/amazon-click-collect.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91686]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetfacebookmessenger]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Facebook Messenger Chat]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Support & Online Chat]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Let&#39;s make it easier for your customers to contact you with Facebook Messenger. Many of your customers are already using Facebook Messenger]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/support-online-chat/91686-facebook-messenger-chat.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91686.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Let&#39;s make it easier for your customers to contact you with Facebook Messenger. Many of your customers are already using Facebook Messenger. It&#39;s time to give them the option to chat with you in a way that feels familiar, trustworthy, and fun.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get back to your customers faster in a way they enjoy&nbsp;When someone has a question about your business, chances are they&rsquo;re just going to leave your site altogether rather than searching for a support email. With so many options out there, people are too busy to spend time looking for answers. But when you give them the option to easily contact you via Facebook Messenger right from your website, this feels like a quicker, more familiar way to get in touch. You can get back to them just a few hours later and they will get your reply directly to their mobile device. No more replies getting lost in an inbox with (probably) hundreds of emails!&nbsp;Customize the user experience &nbsp;Choose if you want to have just one person that can be contacted or multiple team members&mdash;it&rsquo;s possible to add every one of your teammates. In addition, you can select different types of designs for the contact button itself, including animations, location on the screen, its general style, and more.&nbsp;Fully functional across desktop &amp; mobileDesktop: If customers have Facebook Messenger installed on their desktop, it will open the app. If they don&#39;t have it installed, it will open in Messenger Web.Mobile: Facebook Messenger app will be opened right away.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1594152-pprod/facebook-messenger-chat.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1594152-pbig/facebook-messenger-chat.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91884]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetluckywheel]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Lucky wheel]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Contests]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Lucky Wheel allows you to add a customizable spinning wheel to your website. Offer potential customers discounts on exchange for their email address, name, phone number, or other information]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/contests/91884-lucky-wheel.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91884.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Lucky Wheel allows you to add a customizable spinning wheel to your website. Offer potential customers discounts on exchange for their email address, name, phone number, or other information.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The Lucky Wheel module offers a compelling advantage for e-commerce businesses utilizing PrestaShop, enhancing customer engagement and conversion rates. This interactive tool adds an element of gamification to the shopping experience, enticing visitors to spin the wheel for exclusive discounts, special offers, or other incentives.&nbsp;By tapping into the innate human desire for surprises and rewards, the Lucky Wheel module effectively captures and maintains user attention, reducing bounce rates and prolonging on-site sessions. This heightened engagement often translates to increased brand loyalty and repeat visits, as customers associate positive feelings with the shopping platform.&nbsp;Moreover, the Lucky Wheel module enables data collection through user participation, providing valuable insights into consumer preferences and behavior. This information empowers businesses to refine their marketing strategies, tailor promotions, and optimize their product offerings.&nbsp;In summary, the Lucky Wheel module on PrestaShop not only entertains and gratifies shoppers but also elevates user interaction, fosters loyalty, and furnishes data-driven decision-making capabilities, ultimately contributing to improved sales and sustained growth.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1597855-pprod/lucky-wheel.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1597855-pbig/lucky-wheel.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91978]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetfaq]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[FAQ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[FAQ (Frequently Asked Questions)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Smartarget FAQ lets you easily surface the most helpful information to your site&rsquo;s visitors, reducing the need for them to contact customer support and increase customer engagement]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/faq-frequently-asked-questions/91978-faq.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91978.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Smartarget FAQ lets you easily surface the most helpful information to your site&rsquo;s visitors, reducing the need for them to contact customer support and increase customer engagement.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[When a customer lands on your site, you can bet they&rsquo;ll have a few questions. But when you answer all of their most common questions right off the bat, you enhance the confidence &amp; trust they have in your business&mdash;pushing them to purchase even faster.&nbsp;You can show the FAQ on every page with questions and answers, links to relevant pages, and your support email or phone number if they do need to chat with you directly.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599512-pprod/faq.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599512-pbig/faq.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91980]]></id><name><![CDATA[feedpricemodule]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Feed Price CSS ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEA SEM (paid advertising) & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save 20% of your Google Shopping' spending thanks to Feed Price]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/sea-paid-advertising-affiliation-platforms/91980-feed-price-css.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91980.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save 20% of your Google Shopping' spending thanks to Feed Price. Our Comparator Shopping Service is Google's first partner in Europe and the biggest players in the market such as Mano Mano, Sarenza and Cultura use us on a daily basis.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Google CSS Partner Premium : Feed Price is the leading CSS provider in Europe. Quick set-up: just 15 minutes once your account has been validated to benefit from the 20% discount.Budget savings: you save up to 20% on your CPCs.CSS tested and approved by many merchants: over 1,500 merchants listed, 80 million products.Launch without interruption or loss of history: module installation is quick and easy, with no risk to your product referencing or Analytics statistics.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599515-pprod/feed-price-css.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599515-pbig/feed-price-css.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[91982]]></id><name><![CDATA[wnetsecurity]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Waynet Security]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Security & Access]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Thanks to this module, your store will be automatically scanned every day for security vulnerabilities. This will allow you to quickly detect potential danger and secure your store]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/website-security-access/91982-waynet-security.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/91982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Thanks to this module, your store will be automatically scanned every day for security vulnerabilities. This will allow you to quickly detect potential danger and secure your store.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[When developing your store, you use many modules and templates. In some of them, after some time, bugs that cause security vulnerabilities may be discovered. Thanks to our solution, your store will be scanned daily, and you will receive a report and be able to act quickly in the event of a problem.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599523-pprod/waynet-security.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1599523-pbig/waynet-security.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92049]]></id><name><![CDATA[happycalendar]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Happy Calendar]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Blog, Forum & News]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Highlight your product launches, upcoming events, or key dates in an intuitive and engaging way with Happy Calendar]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/blog-forum-new/92049-happy-calendar.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92049.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Highlight your product launches, upcoming events, or key dates in an intuitive and engaging way with Happy Calendar. Don't let your customers miss these pivotal moments for your site!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increased Visibility: Highlight the key moments of your shop, thereby increasing traffic and engagement during these crucial periods.Optimized Conversions: Turn customer anticipation into actual purchases, capitalizing on the events you've showcased.Strengthened Customer Loyalty: Provide an enriched and continuous user experience, thereby reinforcing customer loyalty and encouraging return visits.Competitive Advantage: Stand out from the competition by offering a unique and interactive experience around your events and launches.Sustained Customer Relationship: By allowing them to stay informed about upcoming events, you maintain a continuous relationship with your customers, keeping them engaged in the long run.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1600221-pprod/happy-calendar.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1600221-pbig/happy-calendar.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92051]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetreviews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Reviews]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Customer Reviews]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allowing customers to leave a review on your website has a great benefit of gaining trust by other customers to increase the chance that they will also buy]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/customer-reviews/92051-reviews.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92051.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allowing customers to leave a review on your website has a great benefit of gaining trust by other customers to increase the chance that they will also buy. This review app gives you full control on reviews!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Do you ever get good feedback from your customers? Share that feedback on your Prestashop site as social proof to build trust with prospective customers and increase their trust make them buy on your website with Smartarget Reviews.&nbsp;One of the biggest benefits of Smartarget Reviews is that you can avoid showing non-constructive feedback. You work hard on your website, but sometimes non-constructive customers leave aggressive reviews for no reasonable reason. Smartarget Reviews allows you to have full control on the reviews you show on your website.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1600239-pprod/reviews.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1600239-pbig/reviews.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92140]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetpopupforms]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Popup Forms]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pop-up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Popup forms on PrestaShop capture emails with attention-grabbing incentives, timed triggers, growing your mailing list effectively]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/pop-up/92140-popup-forms.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92140.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Popup forms on PrestaShop capture emails with attention-grabbing incentives, timed triggers, growing your mailing list effectively]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You spend a lot of time and money to bring customers to your website, you better want to have their email in order to make sure they will get your newsletter in the future. Using Popup Forms by Smartarget will help you to collect emails of customers by showing a popup when they visit your website.&nbsp;Newsletters could be a powerful marketing tool to bring back customers or to make potential customers buy your product and service for the first time. With Newsletter you can offer incentives for users, tell them about new products or services, etc. But the first step is to get their email so they become a lead. With Popup Forms by Smartarget you can design your own popup very quickly and start collecting emails.&nbsp;It&rsquo;s that simple for you to start growing your mailing list. As much as more users visit your website, you can be sure that your mailing list will grow by using our app.&nbsp;You don&rsquo;t need to have any coding skills or help from developers to configure your Popup Forms and show it on your website. It takes only a few minutes to create the popup of your dreams.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1601311-pprod/popup-forms.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1601311-pbig/popup-forms.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92278]]></id><name><![CDATA[btecommercecopilot]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[E-commerce Copilot - Generate & Translate with chatGPT4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[International & Localization]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save time with your E-commerce Copilot. Use GPT-4 artificial intelligence to assist you in the creation and translation of product descriptions, categories and CMS pages]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/international-localization/92278-e-commerce-copilot-generate-translate-with-chatgpt4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92278.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save time with your E-commerce Copilot. Use GPT-4 artificial intelligence to assist you in the creation and translation of product descriptions, categories and CMS pages. Keep control over AI-generated content.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The daily task of writing product descriptions can be tedious and time-consuming. And we know that your time is precious. That&#39;s why we&#39;re providing you with an e-commerce co-pilot that will help you create the best possible, SEO-optimized descriptions in the shortest possible time.&nbsp;Our &quot;E-commerce Copilot&quot; module lets you use the power of GPT-4 artificial intelligence to generate your product and category descriptions, as well as the content of your CMS pages. Don&#39;t spend hours manually writing your product descriptions: team up with a qualified partner and save time every day!&nbsp;SAVE TIME EVERY DAY&nbsp;The module installs&nbsp;an e-commerce content writing wizard&nbsp;on your PrestaShop store, saving you time every day: choose the type of content you want to write (short, long or meta description of a product or category, CMS page content), ask the AI to generate it, proofread it, modify it if necessary, then save! In just a few clicks, you&#39;ll have a complete, SEO-optimized text with minimum effort. In the same way, you can ask GPT-4 to translate content into any of your store&#39;s languages.We&#39;ve already drawn up prompts for you to send to GPT-4, so that you can start using the module as soon as it&#39;s installed, and save time in the process. However, if for any reason you&#39;d like to write your own prompts, you can! A tab in the module configuration is dedicated to customizing prompts.Finally, there&#39;s no need to go outside the product creation forms to use AI: we&#39;ve integrated the tool for generating and translating product descriptions directly within the forms. This allows you to enlist the help of your co-pilot directly during the product creation process! You can also call on your e-commerce assistant at any time, wherever you are in the back office of your PrestaShop store. The AI can be accessed directly via a menu section in your PrestaShop store.&nbsp;KEEP CONTROL OVER THE QUALITY OF YOUR CONTENT&nbsp;Artificial Intelligence is powerful, but it can&#39;t completely replace you. That&#39;s why we&#39;ve made it a point of honor to let you control the content generated, ensuring that the text is consistent and perfectly reflects your vision and the style of your store. Once your approval has been obtained, the module automatically saves the new texts or translations.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[i18n_localization]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1602584-pprod/e-commerce-copilot-generate-translate-with-chatgpt4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1602584-pbig/e-commerce-copilot-generate-translate-with-chatgpt4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92292]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetsocialproofsales]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Social Proof Sales]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Promotions & Gifts]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Show notifications of previous sales on your website to get more trust by new and existing customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/promotions-gifts/92292-social-proof-sales.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92292.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Show notifications of previous sales on your website to get more trust by new and existing customers. Using Social Proof Sales by Smartarget will show random notifications of products that you pick only.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Create a pool of names and a pool of items you want to promote and the Social Proof Sales app will show it on your website. This app can help your users to gain more trust and for you to have more sales!&nbsp;Pick the right user experience you want&nbsp;You can choose what items to promote, add relevant pictures and customers names. Pick the position of the notification, how many notifications to show and the frequency.&nbsp;It doesn&#39;t matter if your website is new or already running for many years, with Social Proof Sales you can manually add notifications and make your new customers aware of previous sales.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1602640-pprod/social-proof-sales.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1602640-pbig/social-proof-sales.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92402]]></id><name><![CDATA[addonvalidatecustomer]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Validate Users at Registration]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Customer Administration]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This Prestashop Validate Users at Registration Module allows admins to validates new user registrations and also offers various features for admin approval, email notifications, and auto-assigning cus]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/customer-administration/92402-validate-users-at-registration.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92402.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This Prestashop Validate Users at Registration Module allows admins to validates new user registrations and also offers various features for admin approval, email notifications, and auto-assigning customer groups.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[PrestaShop Validate New Users at Registration Module offers many important features that can help you get your eCommerce game to next level. Enhanced Security: By requiring admin approval for new user registrations, the module helps prevent fraudulent or unauthorized accounts from accessing the website. This added layer of security can protect the merchant from potential scams or malicious activities. Quality Control: Admin approval ensures that only legitimate users gain access to the online store. This can help maintain a higher standard of quality among the customer base, reducing the likelihood of fake or spam accounts. Customized User Group Assignment: The ability to auto-assign user groups allows merchants to segment their customer base effectively. Different user groups can be associated with specific pricing, discounts, or access privileges. This customization can lead to targeted marketing efforts and improved customer experiences. Communication Efficiency: Email notifications for account approval and pending requests keep users informed about the status of their registrations. This proactive communication helps build trust and engagement with customers. Reduced Workload: Automation of user group assignment and email notifications streamlines administrative tasks. This frees up admin resources to focus on other critical aspects of managing the online store, such as product management, customer support, and marketing. Targeted Marketing: User groups enable merchants to tailor marketing campaigns and promotions to specific segments of their customer base. This targeted approach can lead to higher conversion rates and increased sales. Validate Users at Registration Module provides merchants with tools to enhance security, streamline administrative tasks, improve communication, and optimize customer management. These benefits collectively contribute to a more efficient and profitable online store operation. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1603700-pprod/validate-users-at-registration.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1603700-pbig/validate-users-at-registration.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92479]]></id><name><![CDATA[aireviewgenerator]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[AI Review Generator ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Customer Reviews]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Automatically Generate Human Like Reviews on your Products with our highly advance AI Review Generator Module]]></description><author><![CDATA[FME Modules]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/customer-reviews/92479-ai-review-generator.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92479.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Automatically Generate Human Like Reviews on your Products with our highly advance AI Review Generator Module. With AI Review Generator, you can now generate authentic, persuasive, and engaging reviews that resonate with your target audience.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Welcome to the future of e-commerce product reviews! Our PrestaShop AI Review Generator module has been designed to transform how you manage and showcase product reviews on your online store. Powered by AI technology, AI Review Generator not only automates the review generation process but also offers an array of customizable features to boost credibility, engage customers, and drive sales. Automated Review Generation:Prestashop AI Review Generator module integrates ChatGPT to craft compelling product reviews automatically. Because of ChatGPT advance natural language processing model all reviews generated by our module are indistinguishable from those written by real customers. Gone are the days of struggling to collect genuine reviews. AI Review Generator eliminates the need for manual review creation, saving you time and effort. Precise Review Placement:AI Review Generator allows you to select the products where you want your review to appear. You can select a single product or can also choose whole categories. Rules Based Architecture:AI Review Generator Module has an advanced rules based approach to its implementation. This allows you to create each rule with different criteria's for your review generation. You can select a rule with one single product in it and another rule with a one and more categories. Strategic Scheduling:Timing is everything. AI Review Generator gives you the ability to schedule your review generator process. Plan your reviews strategically by specifying the start and end dates for review generation. Align reviews with product launches, promotions, or seasonal campaigns effortlessly. Star Rating Included:Prestashop AI Review Generator Module also offers start rating feature. Our module allows you to effortlessly create product reviews while giving you complete control over the star ratings associated with each review. With the ability to set lower and upper limits for the rating our module auto assigns stars to each review. Customize the Quantity: Our module gives you the option to select the total number of reviews to be generated for a rule. Tailor the volume of reviews to your exact needs. Whether you need a handful to kickstart a new product's online presence or hundreds to establish credibility for a bestseller, you can specify the number of reviews you want to generate. No Seperate ChatGPT Subscription:At no extra cost, enjoy the full capabilities of our AI Review Generator Module, including ChatGPT integration. With our product, you don't need a separate subscription for ChatGPT. Multi-Language Support: Prestashop AI Review Generator Module is allows you to generate reviews in multiple languages. This enables you to generate reviews in your target markets. Whether you're expanding internationally or catering to a diverse customer base, our module ensures your product reviews are relatable and effective.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1604553-pprod/ai-review-generator.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1604553-pbig/ai-review-generator.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92535]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetcountdownpopup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Countdown Popup - Timer Counter ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pop-up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Countdown popups create urgency, captivating customers and driving higher engagement and timely actions using a Pop-up that appears based on a timer counter]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/pop-up/92535-countdown-popup-timer-counter.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Countdown popups create urgency, captivating customers and driving higher engagement and timely actions using a Pop-up that appears based on a timer counter.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Using countdown popups on your website provides a compelling edge. By instilling a sense of urgency, countdown popups enhance visitor engagement and amplify conversion rates. Whether used for time-limited offers, product debuts, etc.&nbsp;You can use the Countdown Popup to promote a special discount, announce upcoming new items, push more sales for holidays, etc.&nbsp;These popups seize attention, spurring immediate action. Effortlessly integrated into your website, countdown popups elevate user experience and cultivate an elevated conversion rate, establishing them as a valuable instrument for potent marketing and time-critical promotions.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1604897-pprod/countdown-popup-timer-counter.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1604897-pbig/countdown-popup-timer-counter.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92549]]></id><name><![CDATA[xyconnectcegid]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cegid Retail XY-Connect connector Official]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Third-party Data Integration (CRM, ERP...)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Connector Cegid Retail XY-Connect synchronizes your Cegid Retail platform with PrestShop(omnichannel strategy)]]></description><author><![CDATA[WebXY]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/third-party-data-integrations-crm-erp/92549-cegid-retail-xy-connect-connector-official.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92549.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Connector Cegid Retail XY-Connect synchronizes your Cegid Retail platform with PrestShop(omnichannel strategy). Automatic synchronization of products, combinations, stocks, prices, categories, establishments, customers, orders and order statuses.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Connector Cegid Retail XY-Connect module, you gain in productivity, consistency and peace of mind:·         Your online catalog is up to date as well as the prices and stocks displayed·         Closed products in Cegid are automatically deactivated on your site·         You reduce the risk of inconsistency between your Cegid database and your PrestaShop database·         You save time by no longer re-entering data·         Your PrestaShop orders are automatically integrated into Cegid, you optimize the processing times of your orders.·         Secure synchronizations: security token, HTTPS protocol support·         GDPR compliant: the module doesn’t store your data! It only acts as a gateway between your website and your Cegid platform·         Clear and simple: manage your data from Cegid and flesh them out in PrestaShop. No third interface needed]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[export]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1605103-pprod/cegid-retail-xy-connect-connector-official.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1605103-pbig/cegid-retail-xy-connect-connector-official.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92630]]></id><name><![CDATA[ipaidthat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[iPaidThat]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Accounting & Invoicing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[iPaidThat propose une suite d'outils complète pour simplifier et automatiser le traitement des factures, de la récupération jusqu'à la comptabilisation]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/accounting-invoicing/92630-ipaidthat.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92630.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[iPaidThat propose une suite d'outils complète pour simplifier et automatiser le traitement des factures, de la récupération jusqu'à la comptabilisation.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[* Gain de temps* Gestion centralisé de toutes vos factures (achats et ventes)* Visibilité sur ses finances* Anticiper la réforme sur la facture électronique avec une plateforme compatible]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[billing_invoicing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1607001-pprod/ipaidthat.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1607001-pbig/ipaidthat.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92631]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetmessagebar]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Announcements Message Bar  ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The best way to get your customers&#39; attention for a special offer, new items or categories, or any type of announcement you would like to share is by using a message bar]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/92631-announcements-message-bar.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92631.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The best way to get your customers&#39; attention for a special offer, new items or categories, or any type of announcement you would like to share is by using a message bar.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Making sure your site visitors know about all of your latest offers can be challenging. How do you make sure they know about your awesome Black Friday deal? Or new items you&#39;re selling?&nbsp;With Message Bar, you can share any updates you like with your customers in a non-intrusive yet eye-catching way.&nbsp;Message Bar is the quickest way to show any announcement to your audience and keep them informed. Here are just a few ways you can use Message Bar to increase sales, retention, and engagement.&nbsp;You can also be as creative as you like. Show any type of message bar announcement that will help you reach your website business&rsquo; goals. Message Bar works both on desktop and mobile devices.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1607064-pprod/announcements-message-bar.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1607064-pbig/announcements-message-bar.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92665]]></id><name><![CDATA[wkvirtualtryonsaas]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Virtual Try-On SaaS Based]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Visual Products]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Virtual Try-On allows customers to virtually try the products in a realistic way from the comfort of their homes]]></description><author><![CDATA[Webkul]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/visual-products/92665-virtual-try-on-saas-based.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92665.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Virtual Try-On allows customers to virtually try the products in a realistic way from the comfort of their homes. Customers can upload image from system, capture it from camera, or use 3D try-on feature to visualize how the items will look on them.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Despite the growing popularity of online shopping, brick-and-mortal have retained their main advantage i.e. customers being able to try out product before buying them.&nbsp;PrestaShop Virtual Try-On is a great tool that lets customers visualize the eyewear products without putting them on physically. Effectively showcase your products by providing customers a better understanding of exactly how the product might work for them.&nbsp;The extension facilitates the customers to try the eyewear items virtually by:&nbsp;Image upload: Customers can upload the image from their system and see how the particular frame look on them.&nbsp;Image Capture: Customers can capture the image using the camera of the device and visualize what the look like on their face.&nbsp;3D Try-On: The feature captures customer&rsquo;s face from various angles and analyze it thoroughly. All visitor need to do is enable camera access and they can view how the product will look on them.&nbsp;Boost Conversions&nbsp;With virtual try-on, customers get a much better understanding of the product than just scrolling through the images on the product page. Providing an accurate and personalize representation of product will help customer make faster and informed decisions.&nbsp;Reduce Returns&nbsp;Customers get to visualize how the item will look on them before deciding to purchase. This will reduce the chances of returns as they get what they wanted.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1607468-pprod/virtual-try-on-saas-based.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1607468-pbig/virtual-try-on-saas-based.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92725]]></id><name><![CDATA[shootime]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shootime]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Shootime is a revolutionary virtual photo and video studio designed exclusively for ecommerce brands]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/92725-shootime.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92725.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Shootime is a revolutionary virtual photo and video studio designed exclusively for ecommerce brands. Our platform provides an affordable alternative to traditional studios, offering a seamless online experience for clients.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module will share you PrestaShop details with Shootime, and let you purchase on Shootime using your PrestaShop billing.&nbsp;Accessibility: Affordable pricing allows merchants to access professional studio services without breaking the budget.&nbsp;Convenient Online Management: The entire process, from booking to production, can be efficiently managed online, providing a convenient workflow for merchants.&nbsp;Real-time Visibility: Merchants can follow live photo and video shoots, ensuring transparency and the ability to provide input in real-time.&nbsp;Cost-Effective Solution: Compared to traditional studios, Shootime offers cost-effective pricing, making high-quality visual content creation accessible for ecommerce brands.&nbsp;Time-Saving Efficiency: By handling all aspects of production, Shootime frees up time for merchants to focus on core business activities.&nbsp;Comprehensive Service Package: Shootime takes care of everything, from studio setup to booking models and set designers, providing a hassle-free experience for merchants.&nbsp;Modern Adaptability: Designed for the modern world, Shootime adapts to the evolving needs of ecommerce, offering an agile and innovative solution.&nbsp;Enhanced Collaboration: Real-time updates and communication enhance collaboration between Shootime and merchants, ensuring the final results meet expectations.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1608486-pprod/shootime.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1608486-pbig/shootime.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92731]]></id><name><![CDATA[chatyprestashop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger & Chat Buttons: Chaty]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Support & Online Chat]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With over 20 chat apps like WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger, etc you can be where your customers need you mostCustomize the widget to match your brandUtilize triggers & targeting rules to display the cha]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/support-online-chat/92731-whatsapp-facebook-messenger-chat-buttons-chaty.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92731.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With over 20 chat apps like WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger, etc you can be where your customers need you mostCustomize the widget to match your brandUtilize triggers & targeting rules to display the chat button to specific users at the right time]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Add as many chat channels as you want from a list of 20+ chat buttons including WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger, and moreCommunicate and offer support to your customers and website visitors on their preferred chat platform.Get your entire support team to support customers on Chaty without limits.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1608563-pprod/whatsapp-facebook-messenger-chat-buttons-chaty.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1608563-pbig/whatsapp-facebook-messenger-chat-buttons-chaty.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92746]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargettelegram]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Telegram Chat - Contact Us]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Support & Online Chat]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[If you want to offer customer support using Telegram, this is the right  addon for you to use on your website. Show a Telegram button on all your  pages so customers can contact you easily]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/support-online-chat/92746-telegram-chat-contact-us.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92746.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[If you want to offer customer support using Telegram, this is the right  addon for you to use on your website. Show a Telegram button on all your  pages so customers can contact you easily. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Turn website visitors into your next customers Let's make it easier for your customers to contact you with Telegram Contact Us. Most of your prospective customers are already using Telegram. It's time to give them the option to contact you in a way that feels familiar, trustworthy, and fun. Get back to your customers faster in a way they enjoy When someone has a question about your  business, chances are they’re just going to leave your site altogether rather than searching for a support email. With so many options out there, people are too busy to spend time looking for answers. But when you give them the option to easily contact you via Telegram right from your website, this feels like a quicker, more familiar way to get in touch. You can get back to them just a few hours later and they will get your reply directly to their mobile device. No more replies getting lost in an inbox with (probably) hundreds of emails. Customers must have Telegram account in order to contact you.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1608822-pprod/telegram-chat-contact-us.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1608822-pbig/telegram-chat-contact-us.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92812]]></id><name><![CDATA[beyable]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[BEYABLE Experience Platform]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Shopping Cart Abandonment]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Our modules use the data of your web traffic to personalize in real time every stage of the customer journey]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/92812-beyable-experience-platform.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92812.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Our modules use the data of your web traffic to personalize in real time every stage of the customer journey. We collect data about the visitor (historic, level of involvement, pages visited…) to provide the best possible personalized experience.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[99% of the traffic of a static website does not generate 1€. Personalisation is the best way to increase your conversion rate, limit bounce rate and cart abandonment.&nbsp;By personalizing your offer in real time, you can offer each visitor an individual and unique experience!&nbsp;BEYABLE modules are no-code and easy to learn.Easy integration*10 ROI for our customers+30% more visits to the product page+20% basket placement+10% average basket]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1609456-pprod/beyable-experience-platform.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1609456-pbig/beyable-experience-platform.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92834]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetcontactform]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Contact Form]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Contact Forms & Surveys]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Make it easy for customers to contact you for any questions by using Contact Form. Reduce the chance of losing customers by being more available]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/contact-forms-surveys/92834-contact-form.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92834.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Make it easy for customers to contact you for any questions by using Contact Form. Reduce the chance of losing customers by being more available.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[In less than 5 minutes you can add a contact form feature to your website and allow customers to contact your support. Using Contact Form will allow you to get customers&#39; questions directly to your email, easily and fast.&nbsp;You don&rsquo;t need to develop your own contact form or to hide it in an internal contact us page. With Contact Form by Smartarget, you can add an icon on all pages that allows customers to fill in a form, and for you to get it right away. Choose what fields the customers should fill in the form, so you have all the needed information in order to give them the best customer support.&nbsp;Contact Form by Smartarget is the most efficient way to get customers contacting you by using a form. You don&rsquo;t need any development skills to use it. The app works both on desktop and mobile devices.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1609562-pprod/contact-form.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1609562-pbig/contact-form.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92871]]></id><name><![CDATA[smartargetstories]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Smartarget Storeis - Instagram / TikTok ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Products on Facebook & Social Networks]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Smartarget Stories will make your website look much better and advanced by showing stories like in Instagram and TikTok. Use the Stories to promote items, discounts, etc]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/products-on-facebook-social-networks/92871-smartarget-storeis-instagram-tiktok.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92871.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Smartarget Stories will make your website look much better and advanced by showing stories like in Instagram and TikTok. Use the Stories to promote items, discounts, etc.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Having stories on a website can help engage visitors and build a connection with the brand. They humanize the company and can communicate brand values, history and mission in a relatable and memorable way. Additionally, stories can increase time spent on the website.&nbsp;Smartarget Stories bring gamifications and make the customers interact with your website, not just reading your content or product descriptions. Getting the customer to interact with your website, simply makes them much more engaged and increases the chance to convert them to be a paid customer. Also, customers are used to stories which can help you to get their full attention to specific content you would like to share.&nbsp;Smartarget Stories allow you to create multiple stories for your website and include images or videos with music/sound, just like you can do on Instagram, TikTok and other social media platforms. You can add a button with a call to action to generate traffic to specific pages on your website.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1610106-pprod/smartarget-storeis-instagram-tiktok.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1610106-pbig/smartarget-storeis-instagram-tiktok.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[92919]]></id><name><![CDATA[popconvert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Popconvert - 10x more conversions]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pop-up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Popconvert is a tool thats innovates in lead capture, generating high-performance results, increasing conversion rates and online sales with Gamified Experiences]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/pop-up/92919-popconvert-10x-more-conversions.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/92919.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Popconvert is a tool thats innovates in lead capture, generating high-performance results, increasing conversion rates and online sales with Gamified Experiences.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Generate 10x more qualified leadsIncrease conversion ratesImprove website user engagementGenerate qualified audience for Email and SMS MarketingIncrease sales with coupon usageDecrease website abandonment]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.8.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[8.1.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1610581-pprod/popconvert-10x-more-conversions.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/1610581-pbig/popconvert-10x-more-conversions.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>